<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="newchapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="ruinHouseBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>You are lying next to a tear in the ground.</text>
            <text remark="next">You struggle to get up. As you move you look to your left, and notice the Spree River flowing.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">The River Spree originated in the Czech Republic and passed through the city from Berlin, the capital of Germany, before flowing into the Elbe River and into the North Sea.</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. During the Cold War, the rivers of the Spree and Havel were one of the few gaps in the "Berlin Wall."</p>
            </remark>
            <!-- SPLIT: You look across the river, towards the Brandenburg Gate at the South—— -->
            <text>You look across the river.</text> 
            <text remark="next">South, towards the Brandenburg Gate——</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX1984mCWWkKDy8j7g660">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">The Brandenburg Gate (Brandenburger Tor) is located in the center of Berlin and is a symbol of Berlin. It was built under the order of Frederick "the Great" to commemorate the miraculous victory of Prussia in the Seven Years' War (1754-1763).</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. During the Cold War, the Brandenburg Gate itself was part of the "Berlin Wall" and only the East German Border Guards could approach it.</p>
            </remark>
            <text>The fire created black smoke, swaying in the air like black mud.</text>
            <text>January 1st of 1952.</text>
            <text>Noon.</text>
            <text>The Reaper descended into Berlin from its cloudy sky.</text>
            <goto goto="20" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="ruinHallBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>The streets were full of rubble.</text>
            <text>Buildings and vehicles had their shape changed, and are exhaling black smoke.</text>
            <text>Fire comes and goes, as if it was performing a neurotic dance. It soars the sky and immediately descends to the grund.</text>
            <text>Suddenly, something big was blown out to the sky by an explosion, and made a loud noise as it fell near you.</text>
            <text remark="next">It was a T-54, one of the best Soviet tanks, turned upside down.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">"T-54" (here "T" is Cyrillic, pronounced "te") is a medium tank designed by the Soviet Union and mass production began in 1947. Since then, T-54 and its sister T-55, quickly became the main armored force of the Warsaw Pact countries, and were exported to many countries, participating in almost all armed conflicts in the second half of the 20th century. The T-54/55 is considered to be the largest production tank in history, and its total number may be as high as 100,000.</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. The famous "five pairs of road wheels"-Type 59 tank, is an improved version of T-54.</p>
            </remark>
            <goto goto="30" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="ruinHouseBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>You keep walking forward, slowly, as if you were paralyzed.</text>
            <text>As far as your eyes could see, there was no one alive.</text>
            <text>A piece of barbed wire attached to wooden piles fell from the sky.</text>
            <text remark="next">It originally belonged to a fence which divided the occupied area——</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19jzpMoIyJvJmTjXOLz">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">After Nazi Germany announced its unconditional surrender to the Allies on May 8, 1945, the Allies divided Germany into four occupation zones, which were under the control of the Soviet Union, the United States, Britain, and France, and implemented democratization and demilitarization in the occupied zones. And de-Nazification.</p>
                <p class="article-text">After the beginning of the Cold War, the three jurisdictions of the United States, Britain, and France were collectively called "West Berlin". They were surrounded by the "Berlin Wall" built by East Germany. They were isolated islands of the Western camp in the Eastern camp.</p>
            </remark>
            <text>There are no more living beings here, there is no need for fences anymore.</text>
            <text>A broken ■■ pierced through a pair of pants, revealing its white figure.</text>
            <text>Jet-black ■■ flows from under a shirt. Not even the flies dare to look at it.</text>
            <text remark="next">Not even 7 years ago, at the end of the Battle of Berlin, this city was as desolated as it was today.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">The Battle of Berlin (April 16, 1945-May 2, 1945) was the last major battle on the European battlefield in World War II. There were more than 360,000 casualties of Soviet-Polish coalition forces; more than 310,000 German casualties, and more than 480,000 people surrendered or were captured.</p>
                <p class="article-text">At 21:50 on April 30, the Red Army planted the victory flag on the dome of the Reichstag in Berlin, which marked the complete defeat of the Nazis.</p>
                <p class="article-text">On May 8, Germany formally signed the unconditional surrender agreement, and the war in Europe came to an end.</p>
            </remark>
            <text>If war is what creates hell on Earth...</text>
            <text>Then Berlin today is a graveyard where not even wandering lost souls remain.</text>
            <goto goto="40" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="ruinHallBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>You keep walking forward, slowly, as if you were paralyzed.</text>
            <text>You could feel life in the distance.</text>
            <text>「Do you wish for a savior?」</text>
            <text>——You felt a voice that didn't belong to you coming from the back of your throat.</text>
            <text>「Yes! Of course I do!」</text>
            <text>——Gleaming eyes covered in mud and smoke looked at you.</text>
            <text>When you prayed for them and placed your hand on their forehead——</text>
            <text>You suddenly noticed. Nothing was coming off their enlarged pupils anymore.</text>
            <text>As if they were remains that had accepted death.</text>
            <goto goto="50" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="ruinHouseBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>"Savior".</text>
            <text>You see this suspicious word burn fiercely, and fly high into the sky from the cold ground.</text>
            <text>You lose your reason, and run towards that word as fast as you can.</text>
            <text>However, a wall suddenly blocked your way.</text>
            <text>Cold walls, as if they were made of ice, were blocking your path from all directions.</text>
            <text>You take a deep breath, and see a sight more terrifying than hell.</text>
            <text>There were no fences or lookouts. There was only a pile of hard and cold ■■ stacked together.</text>
            <text>On top of the ■■ there was something akin to frost. It sparkled with a cold light like a freshly bought ice cream.</text>
            <text>You can't hear the sound of explosions.</text>
            <text>Only a silently burning flame that calms you down to your very core.</text>
            <goto goto="60" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="ruinHallBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>When you looked to your side, you saw people running a few kilometers away.</text>
            <text>They're being guided by a strange group. Are the occupying forces scattering, or perhaps are they evacuating people?</text>
            <text>Every road leading to the city's center is blocked by barricades.</text>
            <text>There are many types of barricades.</text>
            <text>Military sandbags,</text>
            <text>streetlights,</text>
            <text>handrails,</text>
            <text>machine parts,</text>
            <text>a T-shaped steel frame,</text>
            <text>twisted cars and tanks,</text>
            <text>and the barbed wire stripped from the fences.</text>
            <text>On top of the barricades there were several ■■'s ■■ hanging.</text>
            <text>One ■■ had its arms stretched out. As if it was trying to protect something with its hardened ■■.</text>
            <goto goto="70" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="ruinHouseBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>You should have realized it already. Below your feet only ashes could be found.</text>
            <text>But you are unwilling.</text>
            <text>Under the illusion of being a 「Savior」, you desperately keep picking up the fragments of their souls.</text>
            <text>You don't know their names.</text>
            <text>You don't know their pasts.</text>
            <text>You don't even know why there are monsters that don't seem to belong to this planet here——</text>
            <text>Stubbornly, you just keep picking them up.</text>
            <text>Then, you heard 「It」 speak——</text>
            <text>「Engrave their feelings into your soul.」</text>
            <text>As if that would bring salvation.</text>
            <text>As if you were a 「Savior」.</text>
            <goto goto="80" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="ruinHallBerlin.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_15_ruinBerlin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>You are lying next to a tear in the ground.</text>
            <text>You are exhausted. Fatigue has reached its max and your mind has stopped thinking clearly.</text>
            <text>Now that you are tired you finally notice. What you are doing is completely meaningless.</text>
            <text>You are not ■■ or ■■, and much less ■■■——</text>
            <text>But you are already too tired.</text>
            <text>Fatigue is taking over every cell in your body.</text>
            <text>Your consciousness is slowly fading...</text>
            <text>Before you fall into a deep slumber amidst the mud——</text>
            <text>You started to think that, in fact, you have accomplished something amazing.</text>
            <text>Although you don't know whether this is the past, the present, or the future.</text>
            <text>A butterfly landed on your fingertips.</text>
            <text>You will fix its broken wings.</text>
            <goto goto="90" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="carNight.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_15_1946.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">……</speak>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="CG18-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_15_1946.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">are you awake?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">You seemed to had a nightmare.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">……</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">(I seem to be in a car...)</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">(Head lying on her lap...)</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">(Tesla...is driving...)</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">...What happened to me? The Divine Key...did it do something?</speak>
            <goto goto="105" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="105" background="CG18-2.jpg">
            <speak chara="einNoFace">No... I guess not... it should have nothing to do with the "Divine Key".</speak>
            <goto goto="110" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="110" background="CG18-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="8_24_war.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">I'm afraid it was a natural disaster that knocked you down.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Natural disaster?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">There was an earthquake, when you passed out.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Earth... earthquake? Did anyone get injured because of that?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">No, it was not as bad as you think. The tremor wasnt very strong. No one should be injured in Boston.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">How...</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">According to Ada's monitoring of aftershocks, the epicenter should be in the New York City area and Manhattan.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Manhattan? Isnt that……</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Hmm... it's where Edison and the others were working.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">But……</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">....That's not the most worrying part.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">When you fainted, Ada also had a short-term breakdown.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">According to the results of its self-test, it was a high-frequency energy pulse that caused the abnormality.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Energy...pulse?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Yes.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">These are electromagnetic pulses that are quite familiar...</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">As well as，strange and terrible……</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">...Honkai Energy Pulse.</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">What...</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">In the worst case scenario... what happened in Berlin may happen again in New York.</speak>
            <goto goto="120" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="120" background="carNight.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>November 24, 1955, 4 o'clock in the morning.</text>
            <text remark="next">State Highway 1, on the Blackstone River at the border of Rhode Island and Massachusetts.</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19ohxbd4UVhPVop55vD">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">US Route 1 starts from the coast of Key West, Florida (Key West, the southernmost town in the continental United States, and only 171 kilometers away from the capital of Cuba, Havana, on the other side) to Fort Kent, Maine in the north (Fort Kent) is connected with New Brunswick Route 161 (NB-161) in Canada, with a total length of 3846 kilometers. It is one of the main roads connecting the 15 states on the east coast of the United States. Since 1957, the functions of National Highway No. 1 were gradually replaced by the newly built Interstate 95 (I-95).</p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text>The Researcher from Lab 42, whose full name is Frederica Nikola Tesla, is holding the steering wheel intently.</text>
            <text>In truth, if she hadn't been so focused on driving, she had reason to believe that she would be more emotionally volatile.</text>
            <text>After that useless guy wakes up... it was going to be left to her as the more responsible one to explain the current situation.</text>
            <text>However....fainting like that due to the Honkai pulse....means this idiots body went into an unstable state.</text>
            <!-- ^ Some revision might be needed. OG line - 不过，会因为崩坏脉冲而昏倒……也意味着不中用家伙的身体状态，进入了不稳定的阶段吧  -->
            <text>...... No, now was not the time to worry about that. </text>
            <text>In the headset was the sound of Ada still trying to dial.</text>
            <text remark="next"> Maybe it was because of the electromagnetic pulse that had just occurred. It was impossible to reach any numbers.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Within the range of an electromagnetic pulse, any unprotected electrical appliances, or anything connected to wires, such as power systems, electronic equipment, integrated circuits, etc., will suffer irreparable damage. Compared to transistors, electron tubes (vacuum tubes) are less susceptible to electromagnetic pulse attacks-but this only pertains to the electron tubes themselves.</p>
            </remark>
            <text>If it hadnt been specially strengthened for the purpose of connecting with Ada, this WS No. 88 would not escape the fate of short-circuit and meltdown under electromagnetic pulses.</text>
            <text>The paralysis of information means the paralysis of society.</text>
            <text>Do you want me to drive blindly into New York like this?</text>
            <text>Wish there was any other numbers that we could reach miraculously——</text>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoNameNoFace">This, this is the Emergency Response Administration and Providence Special Liaison Office! What department are you in?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text>——Oh my God, it really connected somewhere.</text>
            <goto goto="130" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="130" background="carNight.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">We are... Directly under the Schicksal Organization, Laboratory 42 of the Imperial Academy. Dr. Einstein and Dr. Tesla. You may not have heard of--</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoNameNoFace">How could I not have heard of it?! my God, some reliable people has finally contacted me!</speak>
            <text>The young man on the other end of the phone yelled excitedly, and then apologized again.</text>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">I'm really sorry...My name is Yuri Armstrong and I am on night shift today.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">There was an earthquake suddenly and a power outage, and the phone couldn't get through, so when the bell rang, I was very excited...</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Ah, that's right...although I don't know you, I am very familiar with your names because you are all on the "emergency consultation list"...</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">And what is this "Emergency Consultation List"?</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">It is a contact list jointly drawn up by the government and the North American branch of Schicksal Organization, so that the command system of the Emergency Response Administration can operate normally when something happens.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Your names are at No. 12 and No. 13 respectively... Well, it doesn't matter.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">In short, at the moment when the higher-ranking commander cannot be contacted, I, and even all the members of the Administration of Providence...</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...Will accept your command with full authority.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Wait, wait... Are you not a government department?</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Accept our command, what does that mean exacly?</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Um...... you're ask me about that....</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">This is how the regulations were stipulated...</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...Even our special liaison office was established by Mr. President under the special suggestion of Miss Edison.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">If I want me to read it to you, the first on the list is Mr. President, the second is Miss Edison, the third is Miss Planck, and the fourth is—</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Okay, Okay, I think I kind of understand.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Mophead, these people need you to give orders.</speak>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Dr. Tesla, you should let others finish their explanation proper.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I don't feel like dealing with literal government departments...</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Besides, what more is he to explain? Your rank is clearly ahead of me—</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Wait—Miss Tesla, are you talking to Dr. Einstein?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Of course it's her. who else would it be？You rascal！</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">She is the 12th, I am the 13th, you can just let her give orders-am I wrong?</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">……</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">What? Why did you go silent and suddenly sighing?</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Dr. Tesla, with all due respect…</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">The 12th no. on the list...</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...is you.</speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX1+WKqmGUyb3qMnZ46Is"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>		
