<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="newchapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="streetProvidence.jpg">
            <bgm src="03_03_bostonNight.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>The street in front of him was throughly waterlogged.</text>
            <text>Contrary to it being the mid winter weather of November, the water was not cold at all - so much so that it even felt warm instead.</text>
            <text>The wild ducks in the morning, even out of season, was swimming happily on the stagnant water.</text>
            <text>However……</text>
            <text>Everything that really happens in the world cannot be as beautiful as the one-sided perception of a few senses.</text>
            <text>Just like the road under the water, the potholes are uneven, slippery, slimy, and mixed with sharp hard objects that made it simply impossible to walk.</text>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Found the culprit behind our punctured tires.</speak>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <text>The young man looked along where the girl was pointing, and saw a few huge, sharp “shells” pierced into the shriveled right rear wheel of the sports car.</text>
            <text>The water, stirred by the wheels, gradually cleared up a bit, and Welt could see some of the strange dense creatures growing there.</text>
            <text>The gray-white and purple "shells" - the same lime-sharp cones that are stuck to the tires - were huddled together irregularly.</text>
            <text>Can't say whether it was a mollusk or something else.</text>
            <text>In short, if you cut off all the devil's claws in hell and fold them together like sardines--this is probably what you would get.</text>
            <show chara="teslaBiteGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">In conclusion... this concrete road... has barnacles several times larger than usual.</speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Generally speaking, barnacles refer to a large group of animals in Arthropoda, gnathopoda and Coleoptera, which live in a fixed environment. They mainly adhere to reefs, but sometimes they also adhere to driftwood, the bottom of ships, the shells of crabs and shellfish - some specialized species, and even directly parasitize cetaceans (known as "whale barnacles").</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. Searching for pictures of barnacles (especially whale barnacles) may cause discomfort. Please be cautious of your curiosity.</p>
            </remark>
            <text>The fashionable girl gritted her teeth and stated that she didn't want to deal with the dense crustaceans.</text>
            <show chara="teslaBiteGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltEmbarraNewClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Barnacles... Aren't they Sea creatures?</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">It's close to the sea here...however...</speak>
            <show chara="weltEmbarraNewClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBiteGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Of course I know that!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">That's why it's more terrifying, isn't it!?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Those disgusting things that should have never appeared on inland, just burst our tires!?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">On February 22, 1861, countless marine fish fell from the sky in Singapore during a violent storm.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">But the barnacles stuck in these puddles could not have fallen from the sky. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">....Where are we now?</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Portage Avenue... Hope street. </speak>
            <text>The fashionable girl looked at the map in her hand——</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Not far to the left is the Swanpoint Cemetery; Beyond the cemetery lies the trumpet-shaped mouth of the Seekonk River.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">If we want to do field reconnaissance, it's in a triangle like this, from Bensley point to Libet Park, and then to Blackstone park——</speak>
            <hide position="left"/>
            <hide position="right"/>
            <bgm src="03_03_bostonNight.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <speak chara="reannaNoNameNoFace">But the core is still the cemetery, right?</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoNameNoFace">Really, why is it the fate for it to be always something related to a cemetery.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Who?</speak>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedClose" position="center"/>
            <text>The "uninvited guest", completely silent of footsteps, was dressed from head to toe in a special combat uniform --</text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Ah...</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">...Miss Reanna?</speak>
            <goto goto="20" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="streetProvidence.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_PeerGynt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="reaLaughArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">...... Isn’t this dress up today a bit unrecognizable?</speak>
            <show chara="reaLaughArmedClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Uh……</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">（it turns out that the combat suit is neither glittering, nor blue and white...）</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaEmbarraArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Huh? Excuse me?</speak>
            <show chara="reaEmbarraArmedClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Well. It is OK.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Though not to mention that... why is Miss Reanna here?</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Aren't you the Valkyrie at headquarters?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaHahArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Ah, its as you say……</speak>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace"> I guess I'm supposed to be on vacation, just like you?</speak>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaSurpriseGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Really?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSurpriseGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaHahArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace" remark="next">I had booked a ferry ticket to Nantucket to visit the Whaling Museum……</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX1+nM00AVZfqWdagRa33">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Nantucket (Nantucket) is an island in southwestern Massachusetts, USA, and one of the world centers of the early whaling industry. In Herman Melville's "Moby-Dick; or, The Whale" (Moby-Dick; or, The Whale), the whaling ship "Pequod" departs from here, starting the Hunting trip across the world. </p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="reaSeriousArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">But as you can see, something unusual happened early in the morning yesterday.</speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">....but what about you? What are you going to hunt with your bare hands?</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Barnacles are inexplicably growing out of the streets; when you get to the cemetery, once you encounter a Honkai beast, how will you deal with it? </speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">It was a mistake, -- but there's no need to worry too much about it.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Wait a bit longer, and we'll be -- and oh no, The gun has been changed.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">？？？</speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">……？</speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah... Well... We managed to contact a local Government Bureau.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">The Bureau was called...Ugh. what was it called again? </speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Emergency Response Administration, Providence Special Liaison Office. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It is a department jointly established by the SS North American branch and the US government. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">According to their rules and regulations, Tesla currently has the temporary command of the department.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ahem... Thank you very much for summarizing.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">In short, we agreed to meet on the central lawn of the nearby university——</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Would you like to join us?</speak>
            <goto goto="30" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="universityMorning.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeTesla.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="tank" position="back"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose" position="left"/>
            <show chara="alexClose" position="right"/>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose" position="center"/>
            <text>Three people, tall and thin, and two armored combat vehicles that didn't seem to solve the problem at all.</text>
            <text>Looking back at the Valkyrie Reanna, and then looking at these "civil servants" in front of her, Tesla felt a sharp stomachache.</text>
            <goto goto="40" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="universityMorning.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_25_noise.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="tank" position="back"/>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">So... just you guys? These are the men? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...This is it...I'm sorry...</speak>
            <text>Yuri, the shortest of the three, is their representative.</text>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">I work on the night shift... Mbamba is still living in his office... Alex lives in a rented apartment nearby.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Due to the case of communication blackout, only the three of us could gather in a short time... there was really no other way. </speak>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">So, what is happening now is a Honkai event?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">What's the use of giving me a couple of men with weak natural Honkai resistance?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Though thankfully, from what You said, There's a way to solve the problem……</speak>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">...relying on this kind of tank that even the army thinks is old?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">What about the newly developed prototype mechas? Although they have not been mass-produced yet, hasn't a single one of them been equipped for you? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace" remark="next">The vehicle was indeed built from a Sherman II - but it was built with added Tyre alloy walls and was also equipped with high-energy flame nozzles and chemical agent spray vents. </speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">The M4 medium tank was a tank developed and manufactured by the United States during World War II. There are many modified models of it. It is commonly known as Sherman (Sherman) is a nickname given by the British Army, which originated from the "Devil General" William Tecumseh Sherman of the Northern Army during the American Civil War.</p>
                <p class="article-text">At the Battle of Savannah in 1864 (commonly known as Sherman's March to The Sea), Sherman's forces resorted to scorched-earth tactics, destroying much of the Infrastructure of the South and destroying the wealth and fighting spirit of the Southern army and people in inhumane ways.</p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">According to...Miss Edison's statement...The cost of tactical mechas is too high. When dealing with general Honkai conflict, it is better to use this kind of equipment improvised from the ordinary army...More cost-effective.</speak>
            <show chara="alexClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="alexNoFace" remark="next">Just to add something. The so-called "tyre alloy" is the name given by Miss Edison. In fact, it is a carburized titanium (TI) uranium (U) alloy——</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX18qFb5k3RSFaoDOxcnk">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Tyre is the god of war in Norse mythology--or rather, the god of heroes and courage. In different languages, his name is written in: Týr (Old Norse), Ty (Old Norwegian), Ti (Old Swedish), Tiw or Tiu (Old English), Ziu or Zio (Old German), etc.</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. Tuesday (Tuesday) in English actually means "Tiw's Day" (Tiw's Day).</p>
            </remark>
            <bgm src="themeTesla.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="alexClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">——You don't need to teach ME! I developed this alloy!</speak>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">A mass-produced alloy capable of shielding Honkai energy! The next best substitute for Soulium steel!</speak>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">It was originally intended to be used to make the official version of the mechas! But the density is a bit too high and so the engine power couldn't keep up at all! </speak>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Just a cheap patent worth $50,000, and nothing more! </speak>
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">... Ahem.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">So, in the end, it was used as the tank's protective layer?</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">...It's really the sort of bad idea that person would come up with.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">...Do you know what that person makes me feel about this? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Obviously I don’t know whether I’m facing a straggler or a Maxim, but I feel that "we" are the Zulu fighters who have a way to win.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">......Forget it if you don't understand.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">…In short, as the saying goes, "It's better than nothing". Under certain conditions, I don't deny that you can help——</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">——"Under specific conditions".</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">...Miss Reanna. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaHahArmedClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">.....Do you need me to do something?</speak>
            <show chara="reaHahArmedClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Let me to develop a unified reconnaissance and possible assault plan, okay?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">After all, I know better how far they can go with their equipment.</speak>
            <goto goto="50" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="parkWaterTree.jpg">
            <bgm src="horror.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>November 24, 1955.</text>
            <text>At 6:45 in the morning.</text>
            <text>The sky of Providence city just now started to show some rays of light.</text>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">This is Nikola Tesla. Alex and I have reached our reserved positions on the north side of Bensley Point, unfurling the red flag.</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">This is Yuri Armstrong. Have arrived at the reserved position on the north side of Blackstone Park, and unfurled the blue flag.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Roger that.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Let me emphasize again that your combat effectiveness is very limited. Once you encounter a suspicious target, you should immediately spray chemical agents to hold the opponent, do not fire the cannon without authorization, let alone use flame jets to avoid any unpredictable consequences! </speak>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Understood. </speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">This is Reanna Brigantia.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Already arrived at the scheduled location on the west side of Libit Park.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Roger that.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Miss Reanna, please be prepared for maneuvering at any time. Once we or Yuri find a suspicious target, they will notify you as soon as possible.</speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Roger that.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">My maneuvering time is estimated to take approximately 2 minutes at worst; my kill radius can be controlled within 10 meters in the worst case——</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">——Please keep these two figures in mind, and don't cause unnecessary casualties due to misjudgments.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassHeadsetWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">That's it. Hold for 2 minutes and keep 10 meters away.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Lets go.</speak>
            <goto goto="60" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="parkWaterTree.jpg">
            <bgm src="horror.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>The late autumn morning light, through a network of veins that crisscrossed the branches, fell wet on the tracks.</text>
            <text>Yuri Armstrong drove his armored combat vehicle slowly north from Blackstone park.</text>
            <text>Visiting the "battlefield" for the first time, he saw his father's figure in his mind.</text>
            <text>It was a summer ten years ago. He dragged his father, who had just returned from the army, to hear his own stories about Normandy.</text>
            <text>However, his father just coldly said in reply---</text>
            <text>「It was so dark the only thing we could see was the light coming from the enemy's barrels—— What do you think we told ourselves to get the courage to jump in under those conditions?」</text>
            <text>「.....」</text>
            <text>「Nothing. It's because we've trained for that moment over a hundred times during the past 2 years that we were able to do it.」</text>
            <text>「I've stopped asking myself 『Why』.」</text>
            <text>「This is our reality. There are no superheroes in our world.」</text>
            <text>「The first time I dropped from a parachute I was so terrified my legs wouldn't stop shaking, I was back to being a pipsqueak.」</text>
            <text>「...A professional soldier, with enough training, will leave all unnecessary emotions behind—— That's all.」</text>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">(Leave all unnecessary emotions behind—— That's all.)</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">...Yuri.</speak>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...Pathetic, isn't it? I bet my face is all pale right now.</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">...No.</speak>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">...I'm feeling worse than you.</speak>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">...That smell will reach us soon. I'm sorry.</speak>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">???</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Yeah...</speak>
            <text>A very strong smell similar to ammonia began to make its way into the vehicle.</text>
            <text>Perhaps it's the smell emitted by animals when they feel extreme fear.</text>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">I... found it...</speak>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">No, I should say...</speak>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">It found us.</speak>
            <hide position="left"/>
            <hide position="right"/>
            <show chara="peduncle" position="center"/>
            <text>With its rugby ball-like eyes the monster stared puzzled at the moving iron block they were riding on.</text>
            <text>Its structure is difficult to explain... Or perhaps it's impossible to understand.</text>
            <text>Its tentacle-like arms had something in them. Some had an eye, a blade, and even a mouth...</text>
            <text>The tentacles, like barnacles, were attached to a rectangular piece of granite—— Perhaps a tombstone. They moved like a worm, silently and aimlessly.</text>
            <text>The one thing that was clear... is that this creature was the apex predator of this area.</text>
            <hide position="center"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">W-What do we do? The flamethrower? Do we try burning it to death?</speak>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...Negative.</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSadClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">...Don't you dare.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">You need to... calm down.</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Do not touch the red panel... move your hand to the blue panel...</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">That's right... use the blue panel...</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <text>The young man took a deep breath.</text>
            <text>The smell of ammonia was on the verge of making him tear up.</text>
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">This is 「Blue Team」! Enemy spotted! Proceeding to inject the chemicals!</speak>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">I repeat. 「Blue Team」 has spotted the enemy, injecting chemicals now!</speak>
            <goto goto="70" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="graveMorning.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Reanna!</speak>
            <show chara="reaSeriousArmedClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">...</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">.....</speak>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Reanna!!</speak>
            <show chara="reaSeriousArmedClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">.......</speak>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Check your position! Take evasive maneuvers immediately! I will eliminate the enemy!</speak>
            <show chara="yuriSeriousClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="yuriNoFace">Roger!</speak>
            <goto goto="80" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="CG19-0-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>The strongest Valkyrie.</text>
            <goto goto="82" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="82" background="CG19-0-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>She can run over 1km in one minute using her legs alone——</text>
            <goto goto="84" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="84" background="CG19-0-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>She posses potential that can't be matched by any weapon.</text>
            <goto goto="90" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="CG19-0-4.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Ich bin das Schwarz auch das Weiß</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Vor dem Beginn und zwar nach der Ende</speak>
            <goto goto="95" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="95" background="CG19.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">I am the Black Abyss that devours everything, the White Flower that nurtures all.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">I exist before creation. I exist after annihilation.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Divine Key 「Abyss Flower」, 2nd level output——</speak>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="parkWaterTree.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_17_tatakau.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <cg src="shengqiangShock.png" bg="parkWaterTree.jpg" fadeOut="0" fadeIn="0"></cg>
            <cg src="zhanfangPetal.png" bg="parkWaterTree.jpg" fadeOut="0" fadeIn="0"></cg>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX1+Ny96acaorRcQ6snPL"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
