<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="newchapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="tankInside.jpg">
            <bgm src="mid-lude.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <text>That day, around 8 o'clock in the morning.</text>
            <bgm src="04_20_tank.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Well, there's no need to keep staring at the lookout mirror now, "Temporary Chief"?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNervousNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Already... Is it completely safe?</speak>
            <show chara="weltNervousNewClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaSmileGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">This is not the epicenter of the disaster, there is no need to be worried for yourself.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">At the very least, even if there's going to be an attack, it's going to be Reanna with a better view who's going to deal with it first, no?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">We were there to help her tear down the roof of the Rolls-Royce and make it a convertible sports car after all.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSighNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Well... That's also...</speak>
            <show chara="weltSighNewClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">So why don't you just get down from there quickly?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">This is a rare opportunity, so let's hurry up and seize the chance to learn more.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltEmbarraNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Learn more?</speak>
            <show chara="weltEmbarraNewClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSlyWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Mhm. Learn how to use the Divine Key.</speak>
            <show chara="einSlyWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">....What?</speak>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">The "Star of Eden".</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">A powerful weapon created by using the "Herrscher Core" of the previous era's "Herrscher of Earth".</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">We should all know what it is capable of and how to use it.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ada has finished parsing the instructions for us——</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">---Let's get started while we have this layer of barrier between us and the Valkyries at the headquarters.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">...Huh?</speak>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">"Huh", what's to "huh" here, are you a bonehead?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">No matter how good Reanna is, she works for Otto, the Overseer of Schicksal, who you directly confronted!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">We have done so many things that he would absolutely hate, so it's logical that we should be careful and prepare some means for any future eventualities, no?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">And besides, if Edison were to suffer some kind of disaster, either natural or man-made --</speak>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Who else can we rely on in that case but ourselves?</speak>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Do you really think they're just like you, a bunch of Happy-go-lucky idiots?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltEmbarraNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Er...</speak>
            <show chara="weltEmbarraNewClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Listen carefully.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Any other moment I'll put up with you being our lab's mascot...</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSmileGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">We can go traveling, lazy around at home, or you can bully me with mophead...</speak>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">But not today!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You, mophead, and me need to learn how to use the 「Eden's Star」!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">We have to experiment with it as much as we can!</speak>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">This is a matter of life and death!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaDisgustedGlassWinterClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSBDNewClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">.....</speak>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">Umm... do I have to learn that too?</speak>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">That... Divine something....</speak>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">...No need.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You just keep driving.</speak>
            <goto goto="20" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="roadMontana3.jpg">
            <bgm src="8_24_war.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">...That's all I know.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">……</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">My advice? Don't rush to send in troops with no combat experience like you did three years ago.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">That....root....originally....may not....can....have...any....meaning....righteousness....</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">...Local organizations in North America seem capable of doing a good job of reconnaissance.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">...Moreover, they are well aware that their weakness regarding combat effectiveness, So they will not make unnecessary sacrifices because of rashed advance.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">……</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">No...how can that be...</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">But, if that child Edison really was behind this...</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">...I'll take her head off.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Literally.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">.....</speak>
            <!-- 
                original is 主教大人, 大人 is used as a standard authorative honorofic, Grand Overseer has been 
                used in source material before so it seems like a decent fit, Lord would also work since valkyries
                like Rita/Durandal commonly use "Lord Otto" when speaking to him
            -->
            <!-- RENAME: Yes, I'll keep in touch—— Bishop-sama. -->
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Yes, I'll keep in touch—— Grand Overseer.</speak>
            <goto goto="30" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="roadMontana1.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_25_ada.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>Reanna has felt the cold of death from many men older than her.</text>
            <text>Perhaps, for the strong, the loss of human life is just a number——</text>
            <text>In fact, to become a successful general, one must see human life and death as numbers.</text>
            <text>Living together with your comrades and not see them as a single individual—— But as a group—— Is a ruthless path.</text>
            <text>Some may call it an art, but it has never been called salvation.</text>
            <text>War is war.</text>
            <text>War only brings ruin.</text>
            <text>That is something that will never change.</text>
            <text>Even if it is for a good reason, one must endure sacrifices.</text>
            <text>And more often than not, those sacrifices cannot be controlled.</text>
            <text remark="next">「He who uses force unsparingly, without reference to the bloodshed involved, must obtain a superiority if his adversary uses less vigour in its application.」</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">This sentence comes from Clausewitz's "On War" Chapter 1, Section 3. We should not be partial to its meaning; in fact, in the same chapter, Clausewitz wrote: “If civilized nations do not kill captives or destroy cities and villages, this does not mean that they did not resort to violence. It is because they have used wisdom more and more skillfully in war, and learned to use violence methods that are more effective than this primitive and crude venting instinct.”</p>
            </remark>
            <text>The Honkai is right here.</text>
            <text>The Honkai cannot be reasoned with.</text>
            <text>The Honkai does not follow our logic.</text>
            <text>The Honkai is not afraid of our sacrifices, and will not feel bad for us... It does not care to what happens to this world.</text>
            <text>It will not stop its hostility——</text>
            <text>——Until we disappear from this planet, completely and thoroughly.</text>
            <text>From the beginning we were all thrown into this last stand.</text>
            <text>...But even so, we strive for 「luxury」.</text>
            <text>Amid this eternal war, we wanted to see the beauty, rebirth and salvation of humanity.</text>
            <text>Because they are not attributes inherently related to war,</text>
            <text>And because this war refuses to end——</text>
            <text>We keep wishing for more.</text>
            <text>Also...</text>
            <text>I think it's a good thing to wish for more.</text>
            <text>It's a reasonable envy.</text>
            <text>And what makes a person human.</text>
            <text>Luxury by itself is not a bad thing either——</text>
            <text>As long as we admit it's not a basic need that must always exist.</text>
            <text>As long as we understand the things it can bring us.</text>
            <text>.....</text>
            <text>Tesla.</text>
            <text>Einstein.</text>
            <text>Welt.</text>
            <!-- RENAME: It's been many years since I've seen warm people like them in Destiny. -->
            <text>It's been many years since I've seen warm people like them in Schicksal.</text>
            <text>...Perhaps the last one was that person who liked to be addressed as 「H.A.」.</text>
            <text>I wasn't a fan of her skeptical tone... but her presence brought joy to everyone.</text>
            <goto goto="40" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="cloudSky.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_25_ada.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>The last time I saw her was a hundred years ago.</text>
            <text>Back then, the railroad barely reached Chicago——</text>
            <text>And now it's a city housing over a million people.</text>
            <text>In fact, it's not just America the one who has changed over the last hundred years.</text>
            <text remark="next">「Germany」 is no longer an ethnic name. Both empires they attempted to create were failures.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Refers to the German Empire (1871-1918), which won the Prussian-French War and unified little Germany. The third Reich (1933 ~ 1945) was created by forcibly merging German-speaking Austria with Sudetenland, Klaipeda (Meimel), Gdansk (Danzig), South Jutland (North Schleswig), Luxembourg, and Alses-Lorraine, all of which had German populations.</p>
            </remark>
            <text remark="next">The leader of France changed from President to Emperor, then went back to President.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">It refers to the Second French Republic (1848-1852), the Second French Empire (1852-1870) under Louis Bonaparte (Napoleon III), and the Third French Republic (1870-1940) between two failed wars against Germany.</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. Marx's famous "The 18th of Brumaire of Louis Bonaparte" vividly explains the strange aspects of French society during this period.</p>
            </remark>
            <text remark="next">Habsburg stepped down from history and the monarchy was demolished.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Refers to the "Austrian Empire" (1804 ~ 1867) and the "Austro-Hungarian Empire" (1867 ~ 1918) with the Habsburg family as the monarch. After the end of the First World War in 1918, the Austro-Hungarian Empire disintegrated, Austria, Hungary, and Czechoslovakia became independent republics, and the rest of the region was merged into Yugoslavia, Poland, Romania and Italy.</p>
            </remark>
            <text remark="next">The vacuum of power left by the fall of the Ottoman Empire let the Jews' dream of reviving their homeland come true.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">After their defeat in World War I, the Ottoman Empire gave up much of its territory in The Arabian Peninsula, Iraq, Syria, and the Palestinian area which was transferred to the British mandate, with a large number of European Jews moving in.After the Second World War, the Tragic experience of the Jews in the war made their idea of "Jewish restoration of Palestine" supported by the United States and the Soviet Union and other powers, "The state of Israel" declared independence on May 14, 1948.</p>
            </remark>
            <text remark="next">Italy and Greece were no longer just geographical concepts. Turkey was freed from those 「incomprehensive signs that for centuries have held our minds in an iron cage.」</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19yQNaEeMBKin4QUNdj">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Refers to the unification of Italy (1815 ~ 1871), the Greek War of Independence (1821 ~ 1829), the Balkan War (1912 ~ 1913), and the Turkish War of Independence (1919 ~ 1923).</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s.Mustafa Kemal, the founder of Turkey (Ataturk), described the Arabic alphabet as "the incomprehensible symbols that have bound our minds like iron bands for centuries."</p>
            </remark>
            <text>And recently, two major wars took place in our 「ordinary」 world...</text>
            <!-- RENAME: Amid all these changes, the organization known as 「Destiny」 remained stagnant, and shows no sign of wanting to change. -->
            <text>Amid all these changes, the organization known as 「Schicksal」 remained stagnant, and shows no sign of wanting to change.</text>
            <text>As a Valkyrie, or perhaps as a 「War Machine」, this dissatisfaction could be somewhat unusual——</text>
            <!-- RENAME: Or perhaps that meddlesome Bishop took the 「cells that control imagination」 from everyone... -->
            <text>Or perhaps that meddlesome Overseer took the 「cells that control imagination」 from everyone...</text>
            <text>And turned everyone into a copy of 「The Sage of China」, who can't take a joke or have fun...</text>
            <text>They're all the same uninteresting, suffocating 「cold-hearted adults」.</text>
            <text>...Yet we boast of being 「cold-hearted adults」 as a sign of our old age.</text>
            <!-- RENAME: In this very moment, those 「boys」 in the tank's cockpit may be going against the Bishop's wishes. -->
            <text>In this very moment, those 「boys」 in the tank's cockpit may be going against the Overseer's wishes.</text>
            <text>...But what's wrong with that?</text>
            <text>Maybe acting like that is—— Their own style——</text>
            <text>——And this 「machine」 that I am today wants to protect them.</text>
            <text>Because a 「machine」 has emotions too.</text>
            <text>Even a 「machine」 wants a taste of the feeling called 「envy」.</text>
            <text>「Anyway, I keep picturing all these little kids playing some game in this big field of rye and all.」</text>
            <text>「Thousands of little kids, and nobody's around - nobody big, I mean - except me.」</text>
            <text>「And I'm standing on the edge of some crazy cliff. What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff.」</text>
            <text>「I mean if they're running and they don't look where they're going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them.」</text>
            <text remark="next">「That's all I do all day. I'd just be the catcher in the rye and all. I know it's crazy, but that's the only thing I'd really like to be.」</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Quoted from "The Catcher in the Rye" (Author: J.D. Salinger). The original text is as follows:</p>
                <p class="article-text">"Anyway, I keep picturing all these little kids playing some game in this big field of rye and all. Thousands of little kids, and nobody's around - nobody big, I mean - except me. And I'm standing on the edge of some crazy cliff. What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff - I mean if they're running and they don't look where they're going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them. That's all I do all day. I'd just be the catcher in the rye and all. I know it's crazy, but that's the only thing I'd really like to be."</p>
            </remark>
            <goto goto="50" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="connecticutRoad.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_25_ada.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>Confusion arose after a large number of people woke up from sleep and noticed the electronic anomaly caused by the energy pulse.</text>
            <text>However, unlike in panic scenes often seen in movies, order was maintained during this chaos.</text>
            <text remark="next">Leaving Providence through Route 6, we didn't get caught in any massive traffic jam nor encountered burglars trying to take advantage of the chaos.</text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">U.S. Route 6 is a national highway in the east-west direction. The highway starts in Provincetown, Massachusetts, and ends in Bishop, California. It is known as "the most scenic driving route in the United States."</p>
            </remark>
            <text>On the contrary, we didn't even encounter people trying to fight off Honkai beasts with normal weapons.</text>
            <text>Needless to say, this temporary peace was due to the lack of communication...</text>
            <text>I can't help but praise the autonomy of the people of this country.</text>
            <text>Of our 3 helpers from the Bureau, 1 piloted a tank along with the members of Laboratory 42, and the other 2 returned to their 「official job」.</text>
            <text>Even in situations where technological communication isn't possible, information can still be transmitted manually.</text>
            <text>From 1 person to 10 people.</text>
            <text>From 10 to 100.</text>
            <text>From 100 to 1.000.</text>
            <text>The equipment Edison gave them wasn't very sophisticated, but if they're able to reach more than 10.000 people...</text>
            <text>Even if New York becomes a Berlin-class incident, the people will be able to make a stand and stop the danger from spreading.</text>
            <text>Even if we can only contact a 10% of them.</text>
            <text>As for the epicenter...</text>
            <text>...They can leave that to me.</text>
            <text>3 years ago, they called me their 「last triumph card」 and refused to let me leave the headquarters...</text>
            <text>I couldn't do anything. I was forced to see Martha, and those poor inexperienced children die.</text>
            <text>That wasn't a 「combat test」 at all.</text>
            <text>It was like I was watching them fall off from a cliff alive.</text>
            <text>I won't let that happen again.</text>
            <text>This time, I will fully become a war machine——</text>
            <text>——And exterminate whatever that stands in my way.</text>
            <text>.....</text>
            <text>This time, this machine will become——</text>
            <text>「The catcher in the rye」.</text>
            <goto goto="60" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="tankInside.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_25_ada.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <sound src="04_20_brake.mp3"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Woah! Why did you brake suddenly?</speak>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewGloveClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">...What happened?</speak>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewGloveClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="mbembaClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="mbembaNoFace">On the side of the road... a limping person came out...</speak>
            <goto goto="70" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="connecticutFarm.jpg">
            <bgm src="street.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="elaineStruggleFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">Welcome to Hartford, Connecticut!</speak>
            <show chara="elaineHematemesisFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">Cough——</speak>
            <show chara="elaineHematemesisFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaShoutGlassWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You-are you okay?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaShoutGlassWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="elaineStruggleFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">No, it doesn't matter.</speak>
            <show chara="elaineHematemesisFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">Cough——</speak>
            <bgm src="street.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <hide position="left"/>
            <sound src="04_20_fell.mp3"/>
            <text>The unnamed woman fell to the ground.</text>
            <bgm src="8_24_war.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hey! Hold on!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishGlassWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Pale...Hypothermia...</speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">…Her blood pressure is very unstable, she has to be taken to a hospital as soon as possible!</speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaNormalArmedFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoNameNoFace">That'll not be necessary.</speak>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Leave it to me.</speak>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Miss Reanna?</speak>
            <show chara="weltAstonishNewFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaLaughArmedFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">What, have you forgotten?</speak>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">"Black Abyss White Flower"——</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">- But the "divine key" of decomposition and creation!</speak>
            <goto goto="80" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="CG20-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="04_20_Brigantia.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">I am the black rising from the abyss.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">I am the white descending from the heavens.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">I exist before creation.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">I exist after annihilation.</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">To the thirsty I will freely give,</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace" remark="next">From the fountain of the water of life.</speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Revelation (21:6) -- Then he said to me, "It is done! I am the Alpha, I am the Omega; I am the beginning, I am the end. I will give to him who is thirsty the water of the spring of life without cost.”</p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">Divine Key 「Abyss Flower」, 0 level output——</speak>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace" remark="next">Heilige Lanze, die Welwitschie!</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX18O7USd7byF8+J6GxvE">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">This is German, the native language of Overseer Otto. "Heilige Lanze" means "Holy Gun" and "Welwitschie" means "Centenarian Orchid".</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. Welwitschia is the only species of "Welwitschia family" and "Welwitschia". Also known as "Wonderful World". In 1859, it was discovered in the desert of Angola by the Austrian explorer Friedrich Welwitsch. Dioecious. The stem is short and only grows two leaves in a lifetime (opposite, the two leaves will grow indefinitely; the distal end will gradually dry up into strips and gather into piles, making it impossible to see that they are originally two leaves). The roots are extremely long, up to 3 meters to 10 meters, to absorb groundwater. The average life span can reach hundreds of years, and some individuals can even reach more than two thousand years. It is the national flower of Namibia, neighboring Angola.</p>
            </remark>
            <goto goto="90" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="connecticutFarm.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_PeerGynt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">Hey! Are you guys a medic team from somewhere else?</speak>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">Dr. Morgan can't do anything like that!</speak>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaHahArmedFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">No... we just happen to have a, let's say... 「military medical kit」.</speak>
            <show chara="reaHahArmedFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">That's awesome, I gotta show it to Dr. Morgan!</speak>
            <show chara="elaineNormalFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoNameNoFace">Ah, forgot to introduce myself—— I am Elaine Glaston, former Ranger.</speak>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace" remark="next">「Rangers, Lead the Way!」—— Hahaha yeah, that 「Ranger」.</speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">"Rangers, Lead the Way!"（Go ahead, Rangers! "Is the motto of the US Rangers, the equivalent of special forces in other countries.)</p>
                <p class="article-text">On June 6, 1944, on Omaha Beach in Normandy, when the US Army landed in the "White Dog" defense zone, the deputy commander of the US 29th Infantry Division, Brigadier General Norman Cota and the command of the Fifth Battalion of Rangers The officer, Major Max Schneider, met. The Brigadier General asked: "What outfit is this?" The Major replied: "Fifth Rangers Battalion, Sir!" ("5th Rangers, Sir!") The Brigadier General replied: "Well, goddamnit, if you're Rangers, lead the way!"</p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">The person I was talking about, Dr. Morgan, is called Mikhail Morgan, an acquaintance of mine and a pretty good doctor.</speak>
            <show chara="elaineNormalFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">We're also studying this calamity you guys call 「Honkai」 too.</speak>
            <show chara="elaineNormalFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="reaSmileArmedFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="reannaNoFace">All by yourselves? That's impressive.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Wait a sec—— Elaine... Morgan... Don't tell me there is also a Vivian or Nimue too.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">Eh? What's that?</speak>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">Umm... King Arthur?</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX18sNx6bP5ZCa35+JjZ3">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note：</p>
                <p class="article-text">Elaine, Morgan, Vivienne, and Nimue are all roles in the legend of King Arthur. Among them, Elaine, Vivienne, and Nimiao are members of the so-called "Ladies of the Lake" (Ladies of the Lake); while Morgan le Fay is the sister of King Arthur, known as the "Evil Witch".</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. The relationship between Connecticut, Hartford, and King Arthur comes from Mark Twain’s masterpiece "A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court" (A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court)-the originator of modern cross-fiction novels.</p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaErGlassWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="elaineStruggleFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">...King Arthur? Oh, I remember the teacher reading us that in elementary school——</speak>
            <show chara="elaineNormalFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">——Wait, I'm being serious here. So were you guys sent by the Disaster Management Bureau?</speak>
            <show chara="elaineNormalFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Err... Yeah, something like that.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="elaineSmileFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">Perfect. You're exactly what our team needed——</speak>
            <show chara="elaineStruggleFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="elaineNoFace">——As you can see, fighting those monsters with these Browning is kinda hard.</speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX18lD14m4x7Hih5YT4tS"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>			
