<scene id="11" prev="10" title="ピンタ">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <text>"Eagle" was joyous, startled, and furious.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bgm id="竹林伏兵"></bgm>
  <bg img="废弃驿站院内" duration="3"></bg>
  <text inline="true">It was a joy to learn that his subordinates had caught the rat that made trouble. </text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>It was stunning to hear that the "invader" was actually a little girl.</p>
  </text>
  <transition mode="move" in="0.5" stop="0.5" out="0.5" color="#000000" direction="left" custom="default"></transition>
  <bg img="废弃驿站"></bg>
  <text>After seeing the girl, the "Eagle" finally burst into anger.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="center" img="素裳-嘟嘴-背手-远景" duration="2"></motion>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <text inline="true">The soldiers he trained himself had been beaten like this by a teenage girl?! </text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>What an absolute humiliation!!!</p>
  </text>
  <text>In addition to his fury, he was a little surprised.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="002" action="move" pos="right" duration="1"></motion>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" pos="left" img="老鹰-普通-玩玉-远景" reversex="true" duration="1"></motion>
  <delay t="0.8"></delay>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-标准-背手-远景"></motion>
  <text>"Eagle" stepped forward, looking at the girl in front of him, with a lot of doubts in his mind:</text>
  <text>What is the origin of this girl?!</text>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Looking at the entire Northern Desert, there wasn't anyone not afraid of his Golden Sand Gang.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Even the most elite officers and soldiers thought his rule was far and hard, and never conflicted with it.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Who had the guts of a bear-hearted leopard and dared to break through the door, becoming an enemy of "Eagle"?</p>
  </mono>
  <text>He couldn't figure it out.</text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-标准-背手-远景"></motion>
  <text>And—the one who came was still a little girl, she looked at most sixteen years old, her childishness was still there, and there was the youthful spirit of a young man in her eyes.</text>
  <text>And—— her martial arts wasn't bad, even surprisingly good. "Eagle"’s most prided men went into battle, but the four of them failed to capture her.</text>
  <text>What was the origin of this girl?!</text>
  <text inline="true">"Eagle" wanted to ask a question. But unexpectedly, it wasn't him who spoke first.</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>But unexpectedly, he wasn't the one who spoke first.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-大笑-背手-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[So you're "Eagle"? Wow, I didn't think–]</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <se id="01-42耳光轻-1"></se>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.1" range="40" direction="default"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="shake" duration="0.2" range="80" direction="horizontal"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide" img="素裳-呆滞血-背手-远景"></motion>
  <text inline="true">"Eagle" raised his hand and slapped Sushang severely, causing the words to be stuck in her throat.</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>In his turf, he was the only one who got to speak first, and he asked questions first.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" img="素裳-呆滞血-背手-远景" pos="right" duration="2"></motion>
  <text>The girl raised her head, blood flowing from the corners of her mouth.</text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-撒娇哭-背手-远景"></motion>
  <text>She looked at "Eagle" in disbelief, tears in her eyes.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[You… you hit me?? My mother didn't even–]</dialog>
  <se id="01-44耳光重"></se>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.1" range="40" direction="default"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="shake" duration="0.2" range="100" direction="horizontal"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide"></motion>
  <text>"Eagle" slapped Sushang again, this time the force was extremely heavy, and Sushang nearly tumbled to the ground.</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-狞笑-扭头-远景" reversex="true"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[...Next time you bring the captives back, shut their mouths first.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="094" action="show" pos="right" img="砂匪1-远-坏笑"></motion>
  <dialog chara="094">「Yes, Chief.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="094" action="hide" duration="0.5"></motion>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide" duration="0.5"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>"Eagle" wiped his hands and squatted in front of the girl. </p>
    <p>The girl also looked up at him, there was no fear in her eyes, only stubbornness and annoyance.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" pos="center" img="老鹰-微笑-叉腰-中景"></motion>
  <text>"Eagle" held her chin before saying:</text>
  <dialog chara="015">
    <p>[I don't know who you are or what your goal is; </p>
    <p>originally I was a little interested. </p>
    <p>So I thought I might as well listen to your intentions and if you could make me laugh, I might have been compassionate.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-普通-叉腰-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[...Now, you have lost this chance.]</dialog>
  <text>"Eagle" stared at the girl's eyes, the tears still remaining, enjoying the pleasure of punishing the enemy. </text>
  <text>This wasn't his style, but after meeting with the Raksha, his heart was full of boredom. Even knowing that threats and intimidation were meaningless, he continued.</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-普通-抱胸NO刀-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015" inline="true">
    <p>[Next time, you have to know when you can speak and when you can't;  </p>
    <p>you have to learn to be cautious in your words and deeds in order to please your master and save your life.</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-微笑-抱胸NO刀-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">
    <p></p>
    <p>In the future, people who will face each other day and night will never cherish your flesh and blood like I do.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="015">[You are young and good-looking. Skinny and (?) are believed to be likable. To be honest, I intend to sell you at a good price, so you have a few days to be safe. But don't be too happy too soon.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-狞笑-扭头-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[Wait a hundred times for the traffickers to take you away, you will regret not begging me to kill you today, I promise.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-悲伤-扭头-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">
    <p>[“I regret it” and beg for mercy… You have to do these two things for a lifetime, until you die. </p>
    <p>Those who dare to provoke me to the Golden Sand Gang won't escape this fate.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>After all, "Eagle" glanced at the captive, and was disappointed. </text>
  <text>
    <p>The girl sniffed and nodded seriously at him without saying a word. </p>
    <p>Among the various reactions, it was the one that made him speechless.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide"></motion>
  <text>"Eagle" pushed Sushang away, wiped his hands on his clothes in disgust, and turned to the subordinates on the side:</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" pos="right" img="老鹰-撩发笑-远景" duration="0.5"></motion>
  <motion chara="095" action="show" reversex="true" pos="left" img="砂匪2-远-微笑" duration="0.5"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[What are you thinking?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="095" action="img_trans" reversex="true" img="砂匪2-远-普通"></motion>
  <text>The sudden question made the man sweat, and caused him to stutter.</text>
  <dialog chara="015">
    <p>[Since then, you have been restless… </p>
    <p>...What do you want to say? Speak.’</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="095">[Yes, it's boss... This girl, she, she's pretty good... Let's still take precautions…]</dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-撩发-远景"></motion>
  <text>"Eagle" glanced at the man in disgust, who was frightened to take a step back.</text>
  <dialog chara="015">[You served her the [Ki Suppressant Pill].]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="095">[Yes...yes, she did not resist at all. We were worried...she had ulterior motives and would be against you.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-悲伤-扭头-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[A teenage girl, with both hands bound in shackles, she can't use all of her internal strength.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-微笑-抱胸NO刀-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[...And you thought she would be against me?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="095" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <dialog chara="095">[Your subordinate was wrong!]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>The man lost his soul and knelt down quickly. </p>
    <p>He knew that the more gentle and calm the gang leader's tone, the more furious he became.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-普通-抱胸NO刀-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[……]</dialog>
  <text>"Eagle" was very angry in his heart, but  his face remained calm. This was a habit he has cultivated for many years. </text>
  <text>The Raksha upset him, the little girl annoyed him; the self-assertion of his subordinates made him vaguely feel that his authority had been challenged.</text>
  <dialog chara="015">[Take her... put her in the Dark Dungeon, and lock her up with the Raksha.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="015">[They are not allowed to have food, and they must be hungry until the slavers take them away.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="-1">[Yes!]</dialog>
  <text>The bandits responded in unison, pulled the girl up, and pushed her to the Dark Dungeon.</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-普通-玩玉-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[……Um?]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>The man who had just kneeled on the ground did not leave. </p>
    <p>He bowed his head, not daring to look up, but the trembling of his body had already revealed his tension.</p>
  </text>
  <dialog chara="015">[What else do you want to say?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="095" action="show" pos="left" img="砂匪2-远-微笑" reversex="true"></motion>
  <text>The man straightened up as if he had received a pardon, showing a little excited smile.</text>
  <dialog chara="095">[This subordinate has a treasure dedicated to the leader. I hope I can make up for it.]</dialog>
  <text>As he spoke, he magically took out a cloth bag and presented it with both hands.</text>
  <text>"Eagle" didn't stretch out his hand, didn't even look at the cloth bag, and asked:</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-普通-抱胸NO刀-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[What's inside? Where did it come from?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="095">"A sword that cuts iron like mud, taken from that little girl."</dialog>
  <dialog chara="015">[……]</dialog>
  <motion chara="095" action="img_trans" img="砂匪2-远-普通" reversex="true"></motion>
  <text inline="true">[……]</text>
  <text>"Eagle" still didn't pick it up. The man also maintained his posture, and didn't dare to move an inch.</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-微笑-玩玉-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>After a long time, "Eagle" smiled suddenly, reached out his hand to take the cloth bag, and slowly untied the cloth wrapped around it, revealing the true face of the sword in it. [\s]</p>
    <p>He had confirmed that the man in front of him had not concealed or lied, that was enough.</p>
  </text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="3"></event>
  <motion chara="095" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide"></motion>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑" duration="3"></cg>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <dialog chara="015">[Oh–]</dialog>
  <text>Under the faint moonlight, the sword shone with a silvery light.</text>
  <text>At a glance, he knew that this sword was a wonder of the world.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="12"></event>
</scene>