<scene id="07" prev="06" title="圧勝">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="2" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="远处的烟尘"></bg>
  <se id="01-36骆驼车队loop" looptimes="-1"></se>
  <text>Huh, huh, huh, huh…</text>
  <text>
    <p>The hooves sounded again, and the wheels rolled forward. </p>
    <p>Men with swords and greatswords flocked around, guarding the men, horses, gold and silver of the caravan.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Nothing seemed to have changed, everything was completely overturned: </p>
    <p>The merchants have been reduced to slaves, and the robbers have become their masters.</p>
  </text>
  <transition mode="move" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000" direction="left" custom="default"></transition>
  <bg img="BGDesert01"></bg>
  <se></se>
  <se id="01-38踏在沙上的脚步声"></se>
  <text>Boots stepped on the warm sand, and a faint warmth came from the soles of the feet.</text>
  <remark>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>Note：</p>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>Raksha country located in the severely cold region to the north of Shenzhou and often invades Shenzhou's borders.</p>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>Rakshans have distinctive facial features, many have light-colored hair and blue eyes. Some are as beautiful as gods, while others are as ugly as demons.</p>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>Shenzhou people of that time called those with unusual appearances Rakshans, sometimes in a discriminatory sense.</p>
  </remark>
  <text>The place you step on will always sink slightly, causing the center of gravity to shake, as if being gently pulled by the earth. For「Eagle」, this feeling always reminded him of the blood-soaked snow in the Raksha Kingdom.</text>
  <text>「Eagle」hates snow.</text>
  <bgm id="神秘东方"></bgm>
  <motion action="show" pos="center" chara="015" img="老鹰-普通-普通有刀-远景" duration="2"></motion>
  <text>「Eagle」who had won a big victory was expressionless, his gloominess was like a barrier, forming a field centered on him: outside this was the joyous sand bandits, and inside was muddy silence.</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide"></motion>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <bg img="远处的烟尘" duration="2"></bg>
  <delay t="1.5"></delay>
  <text>He should have been in a very good mood, but today's raid was really too beautiful and too successful.</text>
  <text>The seized silver commodities are worth tens of thousands, and even if they change hands quickly, they could make a net profit of seven or eight thousand taels of silver.</text>
  <text>There were nine middle-aged men and women captives, of which there were quite a few high-class goods, and the slave traders who waited for a hundred times to pass by were also a lot of money.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="氛围_第一折_金沙帮众" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>But the most gratifying thing was the performance of his gang brethren.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>It was totally different from the decadence when he first took over the Golden Sand Gang.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono inline="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Although the caravan was in an ambush this time, the bodyguards did their best;</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>after a moment of panic, they quickly regrouped their soldiers and launched a tenacious resistance. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>——But this is what「Eagle」expected. </p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="BGBlood1"></bg>
  <cg></cg>
  <text>「Eagle」likes opponents to resist.</text>
  <text>
    <p>He was precisely the kind of person who finds pleasure and the meaning of existence from challenge.</p>
    <p>The more fierce the opponent's resistance, the higher the value of training.</p>
    <p>The meaning of victory was to bring the highest satisfaction in the ever-increasing value——</p>
  </text>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <transition mode="dissolve" in="1" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="BGSky02"></bg>
  <bgm id="余烬"></bgm>
  <mono>——In the white snow of the Northern Lands, he once believed that this kind of satisfaction had reached its peak.</mono>
  <mono>——He tried his best to escape from the place where his father, brother and his comrades died, and he used politics as a new battlefield, thinking that he would still be able to conquer the situation.</mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>——After being wronged and imprisoned, the new "comrade-in-arms" abandoned him. It was not the pain and regret that made him wake up countless times from his dreams, but the time spent fighting with the Raksha demons.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">——Those who saved his life to rescue him from the dispatched army, were the loyal subordinates who had been left behind by him.</mono>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <text>Ever since then,「Eagle」finally understood that his life would stay forever in that long war.</text>
  <remark>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>注：</p>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>羅刹国は神州北方の酷寒の地にあり、よく神州の国境に侵攻し、戦争を起こす。</p>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>羅刹人は独特な顔立ちをしており、その多くは髪の毛の色が薄く、碧眼である。神様のように美しい者もいれば、悪鬼のように醜い者もいる。</p>
    <p>ㅤ</p>
    <p>当時の神州人は一際変わった容貌をした者を、差別的な意味を含めて羅刹人と呼んだ。</p>
  </remark>
  <text>
    <p>The moment he left the Raksha Kingdom, his life had stagnated. </p>
    <p>The rest of the time was just a walking corpse repeating its worthless actions.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>That’s why he fled to the Northern Desert, captured the Golden Sand Gang, and got a group of loyal soldiers.</p>
    <p>So he tempered, spurred, and tortured them;</p>
    <p>sent them to death and live with them.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Repeating the past,</p>
    <p>avenging the past,</p>
    <p>yearning for the past.</p>
  </text>
  <text>The man named「Eagle」wants to move the time that has stopped……</text>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <event action="goto" to="08"></event>
</scene>