<scene id="10" type="block" prev="09" title="伝剣">
  <se id="01-20拿出轩辕剑"></se>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-专注-持剑-近景"></motion>
  <text>The girl slowly opened the old cloth, took out the family sword, and examined it carefully. </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide"></motion>
  <se id="01-21轩辕剑氛围声"></se>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑"></cg>
  <text>Ancient Sword - Xuanyuan. </text>
  <text>The sword was two feet long, had a golden yellow body, was double edged, and adorned with dark gray patterns. </text>
  <text>The material was unknown, made with neither refined iron nor cold steel, but it was light as air, blew and broke hair, spoke of sharpness and hardness, and was fully worthy of the standards of a famous sword. </text>
  <cg></cg>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bgm id="久远时光中"></bgm>
  <bg img="忆剑山庄"></bg>
  <text>When her mother passed the sword to her, she warned: </text>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>[This sword was passed down by your Taixuan Grandmaster, and it’s my most cherished family heirloom. </p>
    <p>You must put it away, keep it close to your body, and never let this sword leave your side.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>[The true secret of [Edge of Taixuan] lies not in the techniques nor the tricks, but in this sword. </p>
    <p>After you understand Blade Sanction, you will understand what your mother means.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>Qin Suyi said, while squishing her cheeks, then gently spoke: </text>
  <dialog chara="009">[...But if you can’t comprehend it, it doesn’t matter. [\s]Blade Sanction is unpredictable, only your master never cultivated this Essence out of the seven of us; but in terms of martial art prowess, who of us could compare?]</dialog>
  <text>Her mother sighed suddenly: </text>
  <dialog chara="009">[Lingshuang has always been indifferent, and had contempt for profit… but after ten years, people can change.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>[Sushang, you can’t hand the Xuanyuan Sword to her, even if she asks you to. [\s]</p>
    <p>If she asks why, you just say it was me.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="BGDesert03"></bg>
  <mono inline="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Sushang was noisy at first, but when she arrived at the desert, she cried symbolically, and soon was swayed by curiosity</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="BGDesertWU"></bg>
  <mono inline="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The little kid couldn’t hide the words lodged in her throat, without two words, the Xuanyuan Sword topic already tumbled out of her mouth.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Her mother’s expectations were right, Master really asked her for the Xuanyuan Sword.[\s]</p>
    <p>Sushang was honest in nature, after thinking about it, she still handed over the ancient sword with both hands. </p>
  </mono>
  <text>
    <p>Master will never bully a five year old girl, and steal something right?[\s]</p>
    <p>She presented the Xuanyuan Sword to her Master, excitement filling up her heart, like a girl excitedly showing off her new clothes. </p>
  </text>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="3"></event>
  <bg img="回忆-弹剑" duration="3" pos="0,80"></bg>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <dialog chara="007">[...]</dialog>
  <text>Master laid the Xuanyuan Sword down flat on her knees, gently caressed the blade with her fingers, and after a while, she spoke:</text>
  <dialog chara="007">[This is Old Seventh’s [Ebonstyle]?]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>Old Seventh… Sushang was startled, before remembering that she and her mother came from the same sect, ranking seventh. [\s]</p>
    <p>[Ebonstyle] is the name of the Xuanyuan Sword used by her mother. </p>
  </text>
  <text>After Master mentioned something, she remembered she never saw her mother take any action, nor use a weapon. </text>
  <dialog chara="002">[I don’t know, it should be~ My mother said it’s a family heirloom.]</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="3.5"></event>
  <bg img="回忆-弹剑" duration="0.5" pos="0,900"></bg>
  <delay t="0.5"></delay>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <delay t="0.1"></delay>
  <bg img="回忆-程凌霜" duration="4" pos="0,80"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <dialog chara="007">[Oh… heirloom.]</dialog>
  <bg img="回忆-弹剑" pos="0,80"></bg>
  <text>Master said coldly, looked at the sword on her lap again, and lightly flicked her slender finger on the blade. </text>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <text>Sushang was startled, the sword rose into the air.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="5"></event>
  <se id="01-21轩辕剑氛围声" looptimes="-1"></se>
  <bg img="轩辕剑-上升" pos="0,300"></bg>
  <delay t="0.1"></delay>
  <bg img="轩辕剑-上升" duration="30" pos="0,-900"></bg>
  <delay t="4.5"></delay>
  <text>It rose slowly, very slowly, and when it reached the peak, it paused for a moment.</text>
  <bg img="轩辕剑-光华"></bg>
  <text>A beam of sunlight shone on the golden sword body, as if absorbed by the strange gray pattern, it suddenly bursted into the sky with colorful brilliance. </text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Ah…]</dialog>
  <text>Li Sushang looked completely captivated.</text>
  <text>Thinking about it carefully, the sword flying up and down only took around a second. </text>
  <text>
    <p>But to Sushang’s eyes, that was an infinitely long second. [\s]</p>
    <p>She had been with the sword since childhood, but she never thought that it was such a beautiful thing before. </p>
  </text>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑下落"></cg>
  <text>
    <p>During the time that slowed down, the Xuanyuan shone brightly, slowly descending, [\s]</p>
    <p>and when it landed in front of her, the sword’s blade had sunk into the ground without making a sound. </p>
  </text>
  <se looptimes="0"></se>
  <cg></cg>
  <bg img="回忆-程凌霜" pos="0,80"></bg>
  <text>Her master stood up, and shook her robe:</text>
  <bg img="PureBlack" duration="1"></bg>
  <dialog chara="007">[From tomorrow and on, you will work on cultivating your Blade Mantra; after the Blade Mantra has been studied, you practice your Blade Form; once you master your Blade Form, then you can wield this sword.]</dialog>
  <transition mode="clock" in="0.5" stop="0.5" out="0.5" color="#000000"></transition>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑"></cg>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <bg img="牢房-暗"></bg>
  <text>
    <p>Sushang smiled at the memory. [\s]</p>
    <p>Now she was qualified to wield Xuanyuan. </p>
  </text>
  <text>Looking down at the sword in her hand, Sushang suddenly felt a ping of excitement. </text>
  <text>
    <p>Before her rationality intervened, instinctive reactions took control. [\s]</p>
    <p>The girl caressed the sword, imitating what her master did years ago, and flicked her finger on the blade. </p>
  </text>
  <cg></cg>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <se id="01-32铁剑掷出"></se>
  <bg img="轩辕剑-弹飞"></bg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>The sword flew up in the air, whistling, when it reached mid-air, the golden light was dazzling, and shone brightly. </text>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.5" range="40" direction="default"></motion>
  <se id="01-41轩辕剑撞击声"></se>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <se id="01-40轩辕剑掉落声"></se>
  <text>—The next moment, Xuanyuan hit the ceiling, before falling to the ground.</text>
  <bg img="牢房-亮"></bg>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="center" img="素裳-惊讶-普通-近景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[...Oh no.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="094" action="show" pos="right" img="砂匪1-远-普通"></motion>
  <text>The door of the dungeon suddenly opened, light shot inside from the top, and a figure walked down the steps. </text>
  <motion chara="094" action="show" img="砂匪1-中-轻笑" pos="center"></motion>
  <text>The man ignored the commotion all around, and walked straight towards her cell. </text>
  <text>Li Sushang recognized this Sand bandit:</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Sorry, my hand slipped… should it be okay? Did I bother him?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="094" action="img_trans" img="砂匪1-中-坏笑"></motion>
  <text>The Sand bandit fixedly stared at her through the iron bars, and suddenly grinned, his laugh was hideousness:</text>
  <dialog chara="094">[The Boss wants to see you.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="094" action="hide"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[Aiya… I knew it.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="center" img="素裳-嘟嘴-抱手-近景"></motion>
  <text>Li Sushang sighed, knowing that she had been betrayed.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="2" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="11"></event>
</scene>