<scene id="27" prev="25" title="終わり">
  <transition mode="fade" in="2" stop="0.5" out="3" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="阶梯"></bg>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <bgm id="千年之羽"></bgm>
  <text>The stone steps aren't long, but they are winding. 「Celestial Phoenix」 silently descends the stairs</text>
  <event action="achievement" aid="96d0ac44fb43c563"></event>
  <notification>伝記解放：「精衛」</notification>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <motion chara="000" action="show" pos="center" img="赤鸢-标准-垂手-中景" duration="3"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <dialog chara="000">「......」</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <motion chara="000" action="move" pos="right" duration="3"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <motion chara="099" action="show" pos="left" img="朝雨-标准-标准-中景" duration="3"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>Right behind me is a cute little girl. She's nimbly following after Phoenix, sometimes close to her and other times far away</text>
  <dialog chara="099">「......」</dialog>
  <text>The girl didn't say anything, either. Her silence was different from that of the Phoenix guardsmen—the girls were nonexistent people; every move she made had absolutely nothing to do with this world and her voice as well</text>
  <text>Aside from Phoenix, her existence meant nothing to anyone.</text>
  <text>And in this silent mountain, only Phoenix was able to hear the girl’s quiet whisper.</text>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-悲伤-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Master, look—the mountain villa is on fire.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="099" action="hide"></motion>
  <cg img="氛围_第二折_烟雾2"></cg>
  <text>When Phoenix turned around, a line of long and thin black smoke rose up from deep in the mountains like flowers blooming with ink.</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-疑惑-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="000">[em italic]（Suyi...）[/em]</dialog>
  <text>She puts strength into her feet. In an instant, she's moved over ten meters in length...</text>
  <dialog chara="099">「...It's too late, Master.」</dialog>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <cg></cg>
  <motion chara="099" action="show" pos="right" img="朝雨-阴霾（F）-标准-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="000" action="show" pos="left" img="赤鸢-认真-出招-中景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>The girl speaks in a quiet voice.</p>
    <p>She appears before me and blocks Phoenix's path. Ink flowers are quietly circling in the sky above her</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-悲伤-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-冷漠（F）-标准-中景"></motion>
  <text>Phoenix stopped in her tracks, only staring vacantly.</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-闭目（悲伤）-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「...Qin Suyi is dead, and the Sword Mountain Manor is destined to be with its master.」</dialog>
  <text>The girl murmured.</text>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-悲伤-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Master, there's no point in going back. When you show up it will bring ruin to the world and we cannot remove that from our minds!」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="000">「They shouldn't have died.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-温柔-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「So who should have died? You've changed, Master. The previous master would never care about whether a human lives or dies in the first place!」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-疑惑-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="000">「...You didn't mind?」</dialog>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-闭目-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">
    <p>「All my master cared about was how to live—in other words, 『Stampede of qi』.</p>
    <p>Hehe. If a human falls into that trap, they might as well be dead!」</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-悲伤-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <text>The girl shrugged her shoulders, glanced at the black smoke far away and asked further.</text>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-悲伤-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Where is 『Sumizomeka』?」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「No matter how hard I tried, Suyi wouldn't tell me where Sumizome Incense was. Ahh... She died and many things were lost forever—」</dialog>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-闭目-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「But Master won't give up, will he? No matter how much time it takes to find all the 『Hekihan』 『Disciple』s and get them back.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-疑惑-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <text>Phoenix looked up at the sky and unconsciously nodded.</text>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-笑容-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Haha, I believe you can do it.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-认真-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <text>Phoenix was shocked by those words, and instinctively turned her gaze to the girl’s face.</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="eye" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="森林（白天）"></bg>
  <motion chara="099" action="show" pos="center" img="朝雨-温柔-标准-中景"></motion>
  <text>The girl is looking straight at Phoenix.</text>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Her gaze was very sincere, and her smile brimmed with shame.</p>
    <p>Her words were filled with passion, full of respect and trust.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>She's...</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>I feel like he knows her well.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>I spent time with them long ago...</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>I've spent a very long time with them.</p>
  </mono>
  <text>Phoenix raises her brow, blinking. She was trying to get a clear look at the beautiful girl in front of them</text>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-标准-标准-近景"></motion>
  <text>She looked to be about seventeen or eighteen years old. That wasn’t strange—time was frozen in her world, after all</text>
  <text>The girl wasn't real, just one of the countless phantoms created by Phoenix’s wounded brain. But she was all that remained—the illusion appeared and disappeared; it faded away when brightly lit up</text>
  <text>—The woman who once killed him with her own hands.</text>
  <text>Would there be anyone who understood her more than the person responsible for killing him?</text>
  <motion chara="099" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="阶梯"></bg>
  <motion chara="000" action="show" pos="left" img="赤鸢-认真-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="099" action="show" pos="right" img="朝雨-冷漠（F）-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="000">「Please tell me... What kind of person am I?」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「......」</dialog>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-温柔-标准-中景"></motion>
  <text>The seemingly nonexistent girl smiles gently.</text>
  <dialog chara="099">「I'm sure you are well aware of this. It is merely a memory, and the answer to any question that may arise from it cannot be solved at all!」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-悲伤-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Perhaps it's simply the result of my master asking herself a question, or perhaps an introspection that is difficult to accept. Or maybe our casual conversation and letters...」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「My answer is etched deeply into my master's memory, but it will be very difficult to determine whether or not that was true.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-闭目-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Master, all of your current pain is nothing more than an obsession with the past—but that history no longer exists.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-闭目（悲伤）-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-悲伤-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「Oblivion is a gift that removes all the burden of your past. And this world has such vastness to it, so you can go anywhere and do what needs doing—you're free as master!」</dialog>
  <text>Phoenix said nothing. However, she knew this voice was coming from within her heart—her emotions hadn’t been murdered for an endless number of years; they were just buried alive and returned after the girl died</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-认真-垂手-中景" duration="1"></motion>
  <dialog chara="000">「――Please tell me.」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「You really want to know? Once you find out... once your decision is made, it will become Phoenix again. He'll be a person of the past and walk down his old path until he ends up with that same ending as before!」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-闭目（标准）-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="000">「......」</dialog>
  <text>The silence felt very long, but when Phoenix opened her mouth to speak it also seemed extremely short. It was as if she had never existed or hesitated at all</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-认真-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="000">「I want to know.」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「...Yes, I understand.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="099" action="img_trans" img="朝雨-闭目-标准-中景"></motion>
  <text>The girl closed her eyes.</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-疑惑-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「You're Phoenix, and you are our seven masters. My mother died in your hands when I was six years old... She lost control of herself as a result—and ever since that day she has been following me around with her head held high!」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「You had a strong, firm conviction. Immortality and unparalleled martial arts skills — there's no one in this world who can match you—and the first time we met was when I thought that nobody would be less impressed with your abilities than yourself」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「You look like a god, but I think that's something humans can never reach.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-标准-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「When we returned to the mountains with you, everyone rejoiced. The seven of us were all orphans and loved each other from our hearts—but as time went on for so long together...」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="099">「That to you, we are temporary opponents and nothing more than pawns that can be thrown away once they're used.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-悲伤-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="099">「You're the kind of person who, even if you are attracted to him at first... as time goes on and we spend together more often than not.」</dialog>
  <text>Phoenix remained silent. A sadness like a summer rain poured down on her heart, unfettered by anything</text>
  <motion chara="000" action="img_trans" img="赤鸢-疑惑-垂手-中景"></motion>
  <text>Finally, she voiced the question that had been weighing on her mind for over ten years.</text>
  <dialog chara="000">「Zhaoyu, why did you try to kill me?」</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="show" img="朝雨-悲伤-标准-中景" pos="right"></motion>
  <motion chara="099" action="hide"></motion>
  <text>The girl named Lin Zhaoyu opened her eyes wide and sighed.</text>
  <dialog chara="003">「Master, I've been following you for thirty years. Thirty...」</dialog>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="achievement" aid="abf384293a81b6c7"></event>
  <notification>伝記解放：「幻像」</notification>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="2" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
</scene>