<scene id="06" prev="05" title="待ち伏せ">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>At this moment, hundreds of miles away… </p>
  </mono>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="氛围_第一折_烈阳"></bg>
  <se id="01-35炎热沙漠环境"></se>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>A man laid on the golden sand, unable to move. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Beads of sweat emerged all over his body, making him itchy. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>But he was motionless. </p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2.5"></event>
  <bgm id="神秘东方"></bgm>
  <bg img="BGDesert02" duration="3"></bg>
  <delay t="2.5"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Even through clothes, the sand was so hot to the touch, it was burning his skin. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The man tried his best to focus, so he wouldn’t faint from all the heat and pain. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>At this time, he always remembered what the「Eagle」 once said:</p>
    <p>If people like them were caught by imperial officers and soldiers, their chests would be branded with a red branding iron.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>A branding iron was harder than sand and hotter than the sun. Once it touches the skin, it will melt a layer of skin and leave a brand.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>That feeling,「Eagle」said: it's like going to hell.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2.5"></event>
  <bg img="BGDesert00" duration="3"></bg>
  <delay t="2.5"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Golden Sand gang members often speaked of hell, after all they were destined to meet again there.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Hell is a scary place and it’s boring; there’s no gold or silver, no good wine, no beautiful women.</p>
    <p>You couldn’t name a single good thing there</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>But here, as long as they succeed in today's raid, they will have whatever they want.</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="BGDesert02"></bg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>This caravan was said to be larger than ones before, and the「Eagle」had received absolutely reliable information. </p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The caravan from far away brought the families of the rich and nobles, and the car was full of gold and silver treasures.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>If the information was correct, in 30 minutes, all of these would belong to them. </p>
  </mono>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="BGDesert01"></bg>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <text>Thinking of it, he couldn't help but lift his head slightly, looking out of the corner of his eyes to the only man standing.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" pos="center" duration="3" img="老鹰-普通-普通有刀-远景"></motion>
  <bgm id="传奇诞生"></bgm>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>The man looked to be in his 40s, with white streaks of hair, wrinkles, and scars on his face written with hatred.</text>
  <text>
    <p>He was actually younger, but not too young. Looking at the whole face at a glance, only the eyes stood out: those were the eyes of an eagle.</p>
    <p>He looked into the distance, as if hunting for his prey.</p>
  </text>
  <text>He was just waiting for the upcoming prey, and the ambushing Golden Sand Gang were his minions.</text>
  <text>「Eagle」—— that was his nickname, an honorific of respect and fear.</text>
  <text>As long as it was an order from「Eagle」, even if the Golden Sand Gang was to lie on scorching sand for an hour, they would follow it.</text>
  <text>
    <p>There was no need to question, no promises,</p>
    <p>As long as you follow the instructions of「Eagle」, the exchange will be——</p>
  </text>
  <text>——「Victory」.</text>
  <transition mode="eye" in="0.5" stop="0.3" out="0.5" color="#000000"></transition>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-微笑-抱胸有刀-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>Suddenly, a smile appeared on Eagle’s face,</p>
    <p>His eyes changed accordingly. </p>
  </text>
  <text>Those pair of eyes stopped watching, they turned, and slowly turned around—— this was a signal to hunt.</text>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide" duration="2"></motion>
  <text>「Eagle」raised his hand, took a step back, and then took another step back.</text>
  <text>He was withdrawing from the sight of the caravan's guards, and his hand gesture was the signal to attack.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <bg img="BGDesert00" duration="3"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The man on the sand looked forward again and gave a sigh of relief. Though the heated air was roasting his lungs, he didn’t mind. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Far away, dust was rising. </p>
  </mono>
  <se id="01-36骆驼车队loop" looptimes="-1"></se>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <bg img="远处的烟尘" duration="3"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono chara="-1">
    <p></p>
    <p>「It’s coming.」</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Someone whispered.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>The men who had been in ambush for a long time were relieved, the most difficult stage had passed. </p>
    <p></p>
    <p>From here on, there was only victory. And this victory……</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Was something they’ve been waiting for a long time.</p>
  </mono>
  <se id="01-36骆驼车队loop" looptimes="0"></se>
  <transition mode="eye" in="2" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="3" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <dialog chara="099">???: 「……」</dialog>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_棺材" duration="2"></cg>
  <se id="01-37棺材氛围声loop" looptimes="-1"></se>
  <text>In one of the caravan carriages not far away, a coffin stood quietly.</text>
  <cg></cg>
  <delay t="0.1"></delay>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_棺材" scale="2" origin="50%,0%" duration="0"></cg>
  <delay t="0.1"></delay>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_棺材" duration="20" pos="0,-520" scale="2" origin="50%,0%"></cg>
  <text>It is about the height of an average person, the wood is brightly painted with white lacquer, and it was carved with ornate decorations.</text>
  <text>
    <p>From the outside, the coffin was completely sealed with no gaps present.</p>
    <p>Several black leather straps were wrapped around the body of the coffin and bound it firmly.</p>
  </text>
  <text>It seems that the owner of this coffin had spent a lot of effort to completely isolate the contents inside it from the outside world……</text>
  <cg duration="3"></cg>
  <delay t="1.5"></delay>
  <motion chara="001" action="show" pos="center" duration="3" img="奥托-悲伤-标准-近景" delay="1"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>That owner was in front of it at the moment.</text>
  <text>
    <p>A man with blond hair and green eyes knelt next to the coffin on one knee, sliding his slender fingers across the coffin's surface.</p>
    <p>His movements were as soft as if caressing, but as if he had exhausted all his strength.</p>
  </text>
  <dialog chara="099">???: 「……」</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>This person made the coffin with his own hands, so that the contents of the coffin were isolated from the world.</p>
    <p>It was this person who fought against the laws of the world, just to bring his beloved back to the present world. </p>
    <p>Before his wish was fulfilled, he couldn't throw himself away from the world.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>So, among the roars, shouts, and crying from afar;</p>
    <p>among the wailing of camels, the overturning of carriages, the slashing of swords——</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>——The man was motionless, unconsciously.</p>
    <p>It seemed that everything except this coffin had nothing to do with him.</p>
  </text>
  <text>It had nothing to do with him……</text>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide" delay="3"></motion>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <se id="01-37棺材氛围声loop" looptimes="0"></se>
  <cg></cg>
  <event action="goto" to="07"></event>
</scene>