<scene id="02" prev="01" title="少女">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="3" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <se id="01-17女孩沙漠行走loop" looptimes="-1"></se>
  <bg img="氛围-1-素裳过曝-3" duration="3"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <bgm id="佛心禅悟"></bgm>
  <text>The man did not know it, but despite her young age, the girl already had quite the background.</text>
  <se id="01-17女孩沙漠行走loop" looptimes="0"></se>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="4"></event>
  <se id="01-16镜头拉近转场"></se>
  <bg img="氛围-1-素裳过曝-3" duration="4" scale="2" origin="80%,65%"></bg>
  <delay t="4"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text inline="true">The girl’s name was Li Sushang.</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>She was the young heiress of 「Issen Manor」 in Sichuan, the sole daughter of 「Ebonstyle」 Qin Suyi and the 7th Disciple of Empyrea Phoenix.</p>
  </text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="3"></event>
  <bg img="氛围-1-素裳渐近-1" duration="5" scale="2" origin="80%,65%"></bg>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="center" img="素裳-专注-持剑-远景" duration="5"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>
    <p>Empyrea Phoenix, Ebonstyle, Issen Manor.[\s]</p>
    <p>In Shenzhou’s martial world, these were all famed and respectable names.</p>
  </text>
  <text>But here in the endless desert, these were meaningless words.</text>
  <text>
    <p>The desert was an honorless, lawless wilderness:[\s]</p>
    <p>「The strong live, the weak die.」</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-绝望张嘴-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>「Perhaps this is why,」 Sushang thought.</p>
    <p>「This is why Mother sent me to train here despite Father’s protests.」</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide" duration="1"></motion>
  <transition mode="shutter" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="忆剑山庄"></bg>
  <text>Sushang began training when she was only a year old toddler;</text>
  <text>
    <p>Her mother doted on her a lot,</p>
    <p>but she was also extremely strict when it came to her sword training.</p>
  </text>
  <text>Sushang endured many hardships. She’d be awoken from the pain from her training at night.</text>
  <text inline="true">She would cry to her father about this—— but that would only make her mother even harsher. </text>
  <text>Not even the master of 「Issen Manor」, 「Young Marquis Of Sichuan」 Li Shen, could withstand a glance from her mother.</text>
  <text>
    <p>Since then, Sushang doubled her efforts in practicing swordmanship, and was thoroughly proficient in her family's twelve ways of Issin Mnemonics.</p>
    <p>But when her mother took a look, she still shook her head.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Sushang couldn’t understand what the problem was. Was she not training hard enough?</p>
    <p>Why wasn’t she meeting her mother’s expectations?</p>
  </text>
  <text>One day, Sushang eavesdropped on her parents’ conversation at night.</text>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="忆剑山庄内"></bg>
  <dialog chara="009">「In my opinion, the problem is your Li family’s martial arts.」</dialog>
  <text>Her mother spoke coldly.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「Fleeting Swallow and 13 Stances of the Diving Swift are amazing skills in the middle of Sichuan, but how about Master’s “Edge of Taixuan”?</p>
    <p>I shouldn’t have listened to your nonsense and changed Issin Mnemonics.」</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="010">「……」</dialog>
  <text>Her father whispered something, Sushang couldn’t hear him properly, but her mother gave him a cold sneer.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「Okay, so it’s my fault now? Then I’ve wasted ten years on you in vain.」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「I don’t care about you, and you don’t care about Sushang. Unlike you, she’s shown great potential in sword practice. Even if she’s not as good as Fifth Senior Sister, she’s still better than me.」</dialog>
  <text>From Sushang’s hearing outside the window, her mother sounded cold and defeated.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「My Blade Mantra has been damaged, yours can’t be cultivated, what can I say?[\s]</p>
    <p>Tomorrow, I will head to the Northern Desert and ask the Fifth Senior Sister to take Sushang as her disciple.」</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「The Fifth Senior Sister owes me a personal favor. My face is low, but as long as I speak, she won’t refuse.」</dialog>
  <text>Her father was taken aback, then he sternly objected. Sushang was inexplicably terrified when she heard it. She wanted to agree with her father, but she was also curious about what her mother said about 「Northern Desert」 and 「Fifth Sister」.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「——Edge of Taixuan.」</dialog>
  <text>The three short words seemed to have magical powers. As soon as they were spoken, all the noise around them disappeared, and the room fell suddenly into silence.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「Ever since Master passed away, Lingshuang alone has mastered the Essence of Eminence in this world.」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「Since Sushang wants to learn swordsmanship, why not learn from the best swordsman?」</dialog>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="氛围-1-素裳过曝-1"></bg>
  <text>
    <p>Her mother did what she said.</p>
    <p>On the day of Sushang’s fifth birthday, her parents gave her a generous parting gift.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Bidding goddbye to Issen Manor, Sichuan, and her "home", she went to the Northern Desert and learned the 「best swordsmanship」 for a whole decade.</p>
  </text>
  <notification>Unlocked Biography: 「Li Sushang」</notification>
  <event action="achievement" aid="fdc3d5e2f6d96f8d"></event>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" img="素裳-标准-持剑-远景" duration="2" pos="center"></motion>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>
    <p>Ten years had suddenly passed.</p>
    <p>No longer did she yearn for her home, the only thing she still bore in her heart was her mother’s bidding.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Had her swordsmanship improved?</p>
    <p>Had her martial arts techniques improved?</p>
    <p>Did her current self finally meet her mother’s expectations?</p>
  </text>
  <text>…Sushang didn’t know, she still needed proof.</text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-专注-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>And the way to prove it, was through a『Sword Trial』.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-浅笑-持剑-远景" duration="1"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text inline="true">Therefore, when seeing sword holding enemies approaching her in an encirclement,</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>Li Sushang’s mouth curled up into a meaningful arc.</p>
  </text>
  <text inline="true">Needless to say, this smile said everything:</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>the girl’s first 『Sword Trial』,  was today!</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide" delay="2"></motion>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="03"></event>
</scene>
