<scene id="25" prev="24" title="生きて">
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bgm id="侠女之声（女抒情）"></bgm>
  <bg img="凌霜小屋室内"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <text>Li Sushang took a lot of effort to put the unconscious Raksha into the bed.</text>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_奥托重伤" duration="2"></cg>
  <text>Her head was still groggy, and her whole body was in pain when she moved her fingers. This is so, she still relied on perseverance to just accomplish this great cause.</text>
  <text>After covering the Raksha with the quilt, she sat aside and sang a song that was out of tune.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Yiyaziyamejiegeya... Haliya…]</dialog>
  <text>This tune suddenly appeared in her mind, like a dead leaf drifting to the shore.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Eryaziyame...Haliyajieyajieya…]</dialog>
  <text>Ah, when did she hear this song and who sang it?</text>
  <text>Inexplicably, Sushang remembered the appearance of her mother, Qin Suyi.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <cg img="CG_回忆篇_李素裳" duration="3"></cg>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>Suyi, in white garments, squatted in front of her to reach out and stroke her hair gently.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">[At such a young age, it's really hard for you to go to learn martial arts outside the Great Wall for your mother. But Mommy will arrange everything. In the future, when you are successful in mastering swordsmanship, no one in this world will dare to bully us.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009" inline="true">[Mommy has a lot of hardships, and if I told you now, you wouldn't understand. In this world, many things are beyond your control. But…]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">“You have to live, Sushang, you have to live… promise me."</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <cg duration="2"></cg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>The girl's crisp singing came to an abrupt end.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[……]</dialog>
  <text>For no reason, Li Sushang activated Blade Mantra, freezing the Mind Lake into a huge piece of ice.</text>
  <bg img="心湖（3）明镜"></bg>
  <text>Thoughts sank below the water, like thousands of turbulent undercurrents.</text>
  <text>The Mind Lake above was as clear as a mirror, illuminating everything.</text>
  <text>Sushang suddenly felt as if she could predict the future. She knew that the door of the house was about to open, and the master walked towards her with the same indifference as before—</text>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <se id="01-71开门声"></se>
  <bg img="凌霜小屋室内" duration="3"></bg>
  <motion chara="007" action="show" pos="center" img="凌霜-标准-标准-远景"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>Everything's going according to plan.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <motion chara="007" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="007" action="show" img="凌霜-标准-标准-近景" duration="1" pos="center"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>
    <p>Lingshuang dragged her dull steps and walked slowly to Sushang's side. </p>
    <p>There was no expression on her face, as if she was not interested in anything.</p>
  </text>
  <text>Li Sushang looked at the master and smiled instinctively, as if driving away a lingering haze.</text>
  <dialog chara="007">[……]</dialog>
  <motion chara="007" action="img_trans" img="凌霜-厌烦-标准-近景"></motion>
  <text>Lingshuang paused, blinking her eyes seemingly bored, and said:</text>
  <dialog chara="007">[Your mother is dead.]</dialog>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="achievement" aid="f264952df7ffa72c"></event>
  <notification>伝記解放：「秦素衣」</notification>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <motion chara="007" action="hide" delay="2"></motion>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="第二折_结尾_底板"></bg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <cg img="结尾印子"></cg>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="27"></event>
</scene>