<scene id="10" type="block" prev="09" title="剣神？">
  <bgm id="国势倾危（燃）"></bgm>
  <cg img="氛围_第二折_仙人"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono pageend="true" chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>[She said that Master Phoenix was the only true Celestial in this world. Immortal and undying.]</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>[They say that she was all powerful and beyond the three realms. With her hands she could turn Shenzhou over, and with her sword she could bring peace to the lands.]</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>[As the protector of Shenzhou, she’d slain one of many demons.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true" chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>[The imperial court has named her as the Celestial, </p>
    <p>but she doesn’t have a care for politics, nor is she concerned about dynastical change. </p>
    <p>Every emperor who’s about to ascend will visit her at Mount Taixuan.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true" chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>[They say that rulers who are graced by her presence will live a long and fruitful life to see their kingdom prosper.]</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>[And the ones who couldn’t would either pass away unexpectedly or have their dynasty taken from them.]</p>
  </mono>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘2" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[—That’s about it. There was more, but I forgot.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Hmm…]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>The Raksha observed Li Sushang’s expression.</mono>
  <mono chara="001" pageend="true">[Those are merely empty praises. Have there been actual accounts?]</mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘5" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="002" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Actual accounts… Slaying the demonic cult leader Yan Shiluo? Or killing the demons on Li Island? </p>
    <p>Those are dubious tales. </p>
    <p>What kind of examples do you want to hear? My wet nurse didn’t tell me much…]</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘5" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p></p>
    <p>[For instance…]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>The Raksha’s gaze suddenly narrowed.</mono>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p></p>
    <p>[If the Celestial really is as all powerful as they claim, transcending the three realms, have they ever brought the dead back to life before?]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Bring the dead… Back to life?]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001">[Yes.]</mono>
  <mono pageend="true">The Raksha said quietly.</mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The man stared at Li Sushang, but he wasn’t looking at her. It was as if there was something giant next to the girl that was glowing with heat and did the same to his eyes.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="002" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[I, I don’t remember…]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Sushang avoided his fierce stare and glanced at the coffin. Suddenly, she had an epiphany:</p>
    <p>[You’re trying to revive someone, aren’t you?]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="002" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Ah.]</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘14" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Yes.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>The Raksha opened his mouth and let out a meaningless sound. </p>
  </mono>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>He stopped after, his eyes dimming. The light and heat they once contained dissipated in the air. </p>
    <p>Once again, he became the foreigner who would sometimes tell a few jokes or look off sadly into the distance.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘15" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="002" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[That’s right! That’s why you’re trying to find the Celestial… You want her to revive someone?]</p>
  </mono>
  <bgm id="红颜近落霞（慢哀）"></bgm>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘16" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Yes.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="-3">
    <p></p>
    <p>He lowered his eyes.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Isn’t it rather common for ordinary people to have a wish like that?]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>The golden-haired man smiled gently.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p>[I want her to come back to life. </p>
    <p>It’s very simple, but it’s often the most simple wishes that are the hardest to fulfill.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001" pageend="true">[Nineteen years. It’ll be nineteen years after four days.]</mono>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Sigh]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>Li Sushang wanted to say something, but she couldn’t find anything to say, so she only sighed:</mono>
  <mono chara="002">[That’s a long time.]</mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>She was only fifteen years old, and she hadn’t been loved for long by anybody else nor had she loved anyone, so she couldn’t understand the passion that permeated the Raksha’s words.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Nineteen years… </p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001">
    <p></p>
    <p>It all happens in a flash. I have enough time, and so does she.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>The Raksha brushed his finger across the coffin. </mono>
  <mono chara="001" pageend="true">[Once we see the Celestial, she’ll come back.]</mono>
  <text inline="true">— [We]. </text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>For a second, Li Sushang thought he was talking about her.</p>
  </text>
  <text>However, the Raksha’s emerald-like eyes were focused on the coffin, completely unaware of her presence.</text>
  <text>To see the Raksha like this… Li Sushang suddenly felt as if she didn’t want to disappoint him.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘11" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[em italic]([Could the Celestial really bring that person back to life?])[/em]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">The girl suddenly shivered.</mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>She never thought the Raksha had that much hope for the Celestial. At first, she was just going to point him to her master and then let her master help him see the Celestial. It was so simple. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>However, Li Sushang had now wandered into another person’s wish by her own accords. </p>
    <p>A sentence that she’d never paid much care to before was now tugging at her heartstrings. [\s]</p>
    <p>She just hoped… Ah, she wasn’t sure herself.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘18" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[She will… Uh… She will come back!]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>The girl said with little confidence.</mono>
  <mono chara="002" pageend="true">[It’s just… Raksha. When we go see my master… and then… When you see the Celestial… You’ll…]</mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg duration="1" img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘17"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>She stuttered, trying to cheer the Raksha up, </p>
    <p>but the guilt in her heart caused her voice to get quieter and quieter.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="002">
    <p></p>
    <p>[You’ll definitely… Get what you want.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[...]</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘7" duration="1"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>The corners of his mouth formed a faint smile.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="001" pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Thank you, Sushang.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Sushang sat there, shocked, and then realized she had a large dumb grin on face. </p>
    <p>She pouted and looked away.</p>
  </mono>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘17"></cg>
  <dialog chara="002">[Hmm?]</dialog>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <transition mode="eye" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <cg></cg>
  <se id="02-02马奔跑（沙漠）"></se>
  <text>The clattering of hooves came closer. </text>
  <transition mode="move" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000" direction="left" custom="default"></transition>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_百里逐驹2"></cg>
  <se id="02-02马奔跑（沙漠）" looptimes="-1"></se>
  <text>From the edge of her vision, a man and horse came closer and closer toward the same direction that Sushang was heading.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">([Hmm? Master has other friends?])</dialog>
  <text>She saw the rider’s face clearly now: it was a giant man of yellow hair.</text>
  <text>Li Sushang suddenly felt as if she recognized him even though she hadn’t seen anyone else for the past ten years.</text>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_风中奇缘17"></cg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>As if by coincidence, the man glanced at the Raksha and Li Sushang too. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The momentary glance, however, suddenly stopped as it turned into a glare.</p>
  </mono>
  <se looptimes="0" id="02-02马奔跑（沙漠）"></se>
  <mono pageend="true" chara="099">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Motherfucker.]</p>
  </mono>
  <transition mode="eye" in="0.5" stop="0.5" out="0.5" color="#000000"></transition>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_百里逐驹3" scale="2" origin="60%,5%"></cg>
  <bgm id="太鼓乱舞（战斗）"></bgm>
  <text>The brute closed his eyes, but opened them quickly.</text>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_百里逐驹3" duration="1" origin="60%,5%"></cg>
  <text>His face was a myriad of emotions: sorrow, frustration, and pure joy.</text>
  <text>He waved his hand, and despite it being empty, a light shot forth from it— !</text>
  <se id="02-02马奔跑（沙漠）" looptimes="0"></se>
  <cg duration="0"></cg>
  <se id="01-26大刀向下挥"></se>
  <motion chara="-5" action="show" pos="center" img="竖劈-上下(透明) "></motion>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.2" range="300" direction="vertical"></motion>
  <text>Schwing!</text>
  <motion chara="-5" action="hide"></motion>
  <se id="02-01马嘶鸣"></se>
  <se id="02-02马奔跑（沙漠）"></se>
  <text>The ropes that connected the cart to the horse were severed, and they ran off into the dunes in the distance.</text>
  <se id="01-34男沙地重摔"></se>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.2" range="300" direction="horizontal"></motion>
  <text>The cart leaned forward and planted into the sand, tipping forward before falling back.</text>
  <se id="01-30女孩轻功whoosh_02"></se>
  <text>Sushang moved quickly and stabilized herself with the [Gleaming Lotus] move of the Edge of Taixuan’s Guard Form.</text>
  <text>She reached for the Raksha but was met with an invisible wall that cushioned her bottom. It was the invisible barrier that the Raksha had opened.</text>
  <text>They both stumbled a bit but didn’t fall.</text>
  <cg duration="1"></cg>
  <motion chara="097" action="show" pos="center" img="李素裳-特写-坚定"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[!!!]</dialog>
  <text>Faced with this sudden turn of events, Li Sushang had not yet calmed down. </text>
  <text>
    <p>Reason being that she knew that move. </p>
    <p>The move that the man launched was [Ripstone] of the Edge of Taixuan’s [Wrath Form].</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="097" action="img_trans" img="李素裳-特写-艰难"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[em italic][(Who is he? And why can he use the Edge of Taixuan?)][/em]</dialog>
  <text>And yet, there was something that shocked her even more.</text>
  <motion chara="097" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="fade" in="0.5" stop="0.1" out="0.5" color="#FFFFFF"></transition>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_百里逐驹4"></cg>
  <bg img="BGPureWhite00"></bg>
  <text>—The man’s hands were empty when he launched his strike.</text>
  <cg img="CG_第二折_百里逐驹4" duration="15" scale="3" origin="20%,5%"></cg>
  <text>[em italic]To bring forth a sword from formless Ki.[/em]</text>
  <text>
    <p>—Isn’t that the highest of the five Taixuan Essences? </p>
    <p>The one that, from her knowledge, was only learnt by her master…</p>
  </text>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg duration="2"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>[Eminence]?!</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="11"></event>
</scene>