<scene id="03" type="block" prev="02" title="天命派">
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑自信-摊手-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-元气-背手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">
    <p>[Allow me to start from the beginning: to the west of Shenzhou, there’s another continent called Europe.[\s]</p>
    <p>You have different sects and houses in Shenzhou, while there’s only one in Europe, called Schicksal.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑自信-单空手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[The Schicksal Sect was established by three families, it’s said that the patriarchs’ techniques are unmatched in this world. </dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">Schicksal quickly became a force not to be underestimated in a few years, which later, they merged with the Hall of the Divine, the Palace of Heroes, and the School of the Briar Crown, increasing its power on the continent.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-苦笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Schicksal is an overview of the European continent, hence affairs are complex and it would be too much to handle for one person. Thus Schicksal’s power is controlled by three families… three sects, and has been for a thousand years.] </dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-惊讶-抱手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[Wow, a thousand years!]</dialog>
  <text>Li Sushang was very surprised. </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-元气-普通-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[Tsk tsk, that’s truly amazing, few of our Six Great Sects have a thousand years’ worth of history! Is this Schicksal a sword sect, what kind of martial arts do they practice?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-笑容释然-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[There’s swordsmanship, also spearmanship; but the most unique techniques passed down by Schicksal, is what you call [Magic] and [Sorcery].]</dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑自信-单空手-中景"></motion>
  <text>The Raksha raised his left hand, inside was a golden cross. </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-惊讶2-普通-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑奸-单十字-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Based on your culture, it would be more appropriate to refer to it as a Magical Relic.]</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1.1"></event>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_犹大誓约"></cg>
  <delay t="0.1"></delay>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_犹大誓约" duration="1" scale="1.5"></cg>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_犹大誓约启动" duration="1" reset="true"></cg>
  <text>
    <p>The golden chains flashed. Li Sushang suddenly felt her body lose power as her internal strength dissipated. </p>
    <p>After a short moment, everything went back to normal.</p>
  </text>
  <cg duration="2"></cg>
  <bg img="沙漠-夜谈1"></bg>
  <text>She looked at the Raksha’s palm, the golden cross already dissipated, and became smoke.</text>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="right" duration="1" img="素裳-疲惫无神-持剑-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="show" pos="left" duration="1" img="奥托-微笑释然-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">(Eh, this feels…)</dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">
    <p>[This is one of the three Magical Relics of Schicksal: [Oath of Judah]; </p>
    <p>it can seal away Honkai Energy— [Ki] Circulation.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">
    <p>[And what I used to heal you last night, was another Magical Relic called [Abyss Flower]; </p>
    <p>it can heal the human body, regenerate bones and activate muscles. As long as there’s enough Ki, now matter how severe the injury is, it can be healed.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑奸-摊手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[But, two of the Magical Relics you’ve seen aren’t real, they’re both mimicries.]</dialog>
  <text>The Raksha then gently tapped his temple with his slender fingers. </text>
  <cg></cg>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide"></motion>
  <bg img="BGNeuron03"></bg>
  <dialog chara="001">[In here, even Schicksal Sect doesn’t know its existence, it’s my unique Magical Relic— [Void Archives].]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">[Everything I’ve seen, touched, and understood, Void Archives can [mimic] using Ki, and manifest into an entity. [\s]Because of this, I can replicate the power of the three Magical Relics of Schicksal.]</dialog>
  <bg img="沙漠-夜谈1"></bg>
  <motion chara="001" action="show" pos="left" duration="1" img="奥托-微笑自信-标准-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="right" duration="1" img="素裳-嘟嘴-抱手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[...]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>Li Sushang crossed her arms and tilted her head, then she bit her lips. [\s]</p>
    <p>It wasn’t that she didn’t believe the Raksha’s words, but her brain had been turned to mush by a bunch of information.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-嘟嘴-抱手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[...Hold on, hold on. That Schicksal Sect sounds fun, Magical Relics and what…]</dialog>
  <text>Sushang pouted in annoyance: </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-元气-背手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[How did we suddenly talk about cultivation and relics? I know you’re very good and don’t explain in such details. So let’s talk about the Schicksal Sect then.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-汗苦笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Mm.]</dialog>
  <text>The Raksha sighed, then looked at Sushang: </text>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑自信-单空手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Schicksal has a firm control over Europe, after a long time, its ambition swelled and finally focused on its vast neighbors. Twenty years ago, Schicksal sent troops to attack— err, visit Shenzhou, hoping to compete with Shenzhou— err, competition.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">[Your Shenzhou army was strong, </dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-汗严-单空手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">but Schicksal’s Valkyries—  err, Wuxia were able to win the matches, using the help of their Magical Relics.]</dialog>
  <text inline="true">The Raksha stopped talking, rephrasing historical facts into a version that Li Sushang could understand was apparently tormenting him greatly.</text>
  <text>The proof is— even in the scorching sun the Raksha has never sweated, yet at this moment there are already a few large beads of sweat slowly running down his delicate cheeks. </text>
  <motion action="img_trans" chara="002" img="素裳-元气-普通-中景"></motion>
  <text>Sushang looked at his embarrassment on the side, very overjoyed. </text>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑释然-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Schicksal had victory close within its control, but then, the Celestial appeared.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-悲伤-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[That’s when I saw her…]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">
    <p>[What should I say of the Celestial… </p>
    <p>With the wave of a hand, the heavens roared with thunder, the earth froze to ice, and flames ignited without wind. </p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">All sorts of strange sights crushed Schicksal’s formations. The Holy Knights stepped forward, but they couldn’t do anything.]</dialog>
  <text>The Raksha smiled bitterly, and his voice gradually floated farther away.</text>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-茫然-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">
    <p>[Even the strongest Valkyrie… the genius who fully mastered the [Oath of Judah], </p>
    <p>when in front of her, she was defeated…]</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>The Raksha’s eyes involuntarily floated towards the coffin.</text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-悲伤目前-抱手-中景"></motion>
  <text>Li Sushang paid attention to his gaze.[\s]After being with him for around a day, she noticed that although this Raksha man talked and laughed from time to time, but when he looked at that coffin, he would go into his world of solitude and loneliness. </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-笑-背手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[What’s inside there?]</dialog>
  <text>Li Sushang had no interest in fighting but couldn’t help and ask. </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-浅笑-背手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[You’re always speaking to it, is someone inside?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">[No…]</dialog>
  <text>The Raksha shook his head, he seemed confused. His eyes moved up to down the coffin, before looking at his palms again.</text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-元气-背手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[You don’t know? You’ve never opened it?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="001">[...]</dialog>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <bg img="沙漠-夜谈2"></bg>
  <text>[...]</text>
  <text>The Raksha didn’t answer her, his mind seemed to already fly to a place far away, leaving behind an empty husk besides Li Sushang </text>
  <dialog chara="002">[em italic]Sushang waited patiently. She held her chin, watched the Raksha staring into space with an empty gaze, wondering what he was thinking about.[/em]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>(Is he missing his home?)[\s]</p>
    <p>Missing something thousands of miles away, how could she imagine what the old country in the Western Regions was like?</p>
  </text>
  <dialog chara="002">
    <p>[em italic]Perhaps he’s thinking of someone?</p>
    <p>(... …Does he have a mom and a dad?</p>
    <p>Aye, a stupid question, of course he does~[/em]</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">
    <p>[em italic]He couldn’t have popped out of a rock.)</p>
    <p>(What about friends? A lover?</p>
    <p>He probably does… Could he be married?[/em]</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>Does he have a master? Is he a disciple of the Schicksal Sect?)</text>
  <text>The little girl realized she knew nothing about this Raksha. </text>
  <text>Although they traveled together for two days, the girl didn’t say any meaningful words to the Raksha, though she asked his name, but she gave up the memory once she heard strange sounds. No matter how hard she tried, she couldn’t remember anything.</text>
  <notification>伝記更新：「羅刹人」</notification>
  <event action="achievement" aid="c6df415ec80024b4"></event>
  <dialog chara="002">[em italic]（I need to talk with Raksha more...）[/em]</dialog>
  <text>Sushang became a little sad.</text>
  <text>
    <p>She suddenly remembered: once she takes this Raksha to see her master, they would have to separate.[\s]</p>
    <p>There’s only half a day left to get along with him, not saying it was long; it was short, really short. </p>
  </text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Aye… Can Master keep him around for a few more days?]</dialog>
  <text>For some reason, the girl felt even more disappointed.</text>
  <text>She had friends for the first time in fifteen years, enjoying the joy of getting along with them, and experienced the pain of parting.</text>
  <text>The night was long, the two people who couldn’t sleep sat side by side, and the gods didn’t guard their homes until daylight was bright.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="04"></event>
</scene>