<scene id="12" prev="11" title="天•地•螺旋">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="1" out="2" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="BGDesert03"></bg>
  <bgm id="十大恶人（阴谋）"></bgm>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The yellow sands roared under the fiery sun.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Waves of air bellowed across the land, bringing with it an unbearable heat.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>However, Sushang felt like she was freezing from the murderous aura that emanated from the man.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <motion chara="008" action="show" pos="center" duration="1" img="马非马-邪恶-标准-中景"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text>The man was of an unknown age and kept a stubble. A striking scar scrawled across his face like a crimson lightning bolt, only to abruptly end at his lower jaw… It was as if it were falling forever.</text>
  <text>If one looked closely, the man had an innumerable number of scars on his body.</text>
  <text>Without them, he would surely be a handsome man, but those red branches that spread across his body didn’t leave him as a frightening demon. On the contrary, it added to a sort of nobleness about him.</text>
  <transition mode="shutter" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <motion chara="008" action="show" pos="400,0" img="马非马-苦笑-标准-远景"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="show" pos="-500,0" img="奥托-严肃-标准-远景（棺材）"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="-200,0" img="素裳-愤怒-持剑-远景" duration="1"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Sushang, be careful.]</dialog>
  <se id="01-39踏在木板的脚步声"></se>
  <text>The Raksha slowly came down from the carriage and carefully placed the coffin on the sand.</text>
  <motion chara="001" action="img_trans" img="奥托-微笑自信-标准-远景（棺材）" duration="0"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[He wants your sword.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-惊讶-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[What? My Xuanyuan?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-标准-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>She was confused at first, but quickly connected the dots.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <motion chara="002" action="move" img="素裳-严肃汗-持剑-近景" pos="right" duration="2"></motion>
  <motion chara="008" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide"></motion>
  <delay t="1.9"></delay>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-标准-持剑-中景"></motion>
  <motion chara="008" action="show" pos="left" img="马非马-瞥目-标准-中景" duration="1"></motion>
  <text>Sushang stared at the strange man and noticed that his glowing eyes were focused on the Raksha.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="008" action="img_trans" img="马非马-微笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>Suddenly, the man laughed.</text>
  <text>
    <p>The corners of his mouth turned upwards, moving along with that red scar of his. It looked a little unnatural, but he let out a hearty laugh. </p>
    <p>By the time he was finished, the man somehow looked gentle:</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="008" action="img_trans" img="马非马-笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="008">[Hey little girl! Are you Lingshuang’s disciple?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-愤怒-持剑-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[I’m not telling you!]</dialog>
  <text>Her anger widened her eyes to the size of saucers:</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[What’s with you?! Can’t give me a heads up before you wanna talk?!]</dialog>
  <motion chara="008" action="img_trans" img="马非马-疯狂-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="008">[Looks like it.]</dialog>
  <text>Instead of getting angry, the man laughed. He reached out his hand and pointed at the Raksha.</text>
  <dialog chara="008">[Apologies, I have a couple things to say, and then I’ll get right to the fighting— mhm, I want to fight that Raksha demon.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[Huh… Huhhhhhh… What are you trying to do?!]</dialog>
  <text>Sushang quickly returned to the Raksha’s side.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[He’s not going to fight you, he… What are you trying to do? Why are you trying to fight?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="008" action="img_trans" img="马非马-笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="008">
    <p>[I’m sorry, little girl, for breaking your carriage. </p>
    <p>As compensation, I’ll let Erebus take you the rest of the way.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>The man cracked his joints as he spoke to Sushang:</text>
  <dialog chara="008">[The Raksha demon’s actually not wrong. Yes, I want your Xuanyuan sword, but I won’t take it from you by force… At least not right now. Tell me, little girl, that is your sword, yes?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[Of course it’s mine!]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="008">[Heh, no wonder you looked familiar, you’re Lingshuang’s disciple after all. Very well. By seniority, you should call me Senior Uncle. </dialog>
  <dialog chara="008">After I get done with goldie over here we can catch up. I was just on my way to see your Master too.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[He won’t fight you.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="008" action="img_trans" img="马非马-邪恶-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="008">[Aye, he’ll fight cause that’s all he will know how to do.]</dialog>
  <text>The man looked the Raksha up and down:</text>
  <dialog chara="008">[Cause I want to.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[You—]</dialog>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <motion chara="008" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <bg img="BGSky00"></bg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <bg img="BGSky01" duration="1"></bg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>—Suddenly</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="008" action="show" pos="center" img="马非马-闭目-标准-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>The sky was encompassed by killing intent, but disappeared just as quickly. [\s]</p>
    <p>There didn’t seem to be any traces of the man left in the world.</p>
  </text>
  <bg img="PureBlack" duration="2"></bg>
  <text>Li Sushang looked at the Raksha, who was as calm as ever.</text>
  <text>That’s right, the Raksha wouldn’t understand. Only she knew that this meant their opponent had entered the Blade Mantra state.</text>
  <motion chara="008" action="hide"></motion>
  <bg img="心湖（1）止水"></bg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The abandonment of all useless emotions. The abandonment of all meaningless thoughts.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>With no greed or anger, no obsessions or hate, still like water with no dust, like a clear mirror and nothingness.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>This is the Taixuan Blade Mantra, created from Empyrea Phoenix's legendary arts!</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui"></event>
  <motion chara="008" action="show" pos="center" img="马非马-认真-标准-近景" duration="1"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <text inline="true">There’s no doubt about it: the strange man in front of them was the disciple to the Celestial herself, the sole man in the Seven Disciples of Taixuan: </text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>[Tireless Courser] Ma Feima.</p>
  </text>
  <text>Sushang remembered meeting him at the Issen Villa when she was younger. The way he carried himself as a peerless co-leader of the School of Taixuan was unforgettable.</text>
  <text>[em italic]…… Did she have a chance against someone on the level of the Six Great Sects?[/em]</text>
  <motion chara="008" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="BGDesert03"></bg>
  <motion chara="008" action="show" pos="400,0" img="马非马-标准-标准-远景" duration="1"></motion>
  <motion chara="001" action="show" pos="-500,0" img="奥托-标准-标准-远景（棺材）" duration="1"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="show" pos="-200,0" duration="1" img="素裳-愤怒-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[Raksha… Step back, let me handle this.]</dialog>
  <text>Sometime in between, the girl had been overwhelmed by the man’s presence, leaving her voice as quiet as a mosquito.</text>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide"></motion>
  <dialog chara="001">[Okay.]</dialog>
  <text>The Raksha nodded since he had no intention of fighting to begin with.</text>
  <motion chara="001" action="show" pos="-700,0"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>He took a couple of steps back and looked at Ma Feima. </p>
    <p>He said nothing but looked at Ma Feima with an empty stare.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="008" action="img_trans" img="马非马-闭目-标准-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="008">[...Pussy.]</dialog>
  <text>The man sighed and said to Sushang:</text>
  <dialog chara="008">[You’re not going to kill him?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="008">[Hasn’t Lingshuang taught you that the duty of the Taixuan lineage is to slaughter any and all demons?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[He hasn’t fallen to that point yet.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="008">[Haha, it’s bound to happen. By the way he’s doing things, he’ll become much more evil than a demon. Aye, why are you trying to cover for him? The powers that this Raksha demon’s hiding… Heh, it’s far more than anything you can imagine.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="008">[...Oh well, who am I to tell you what to do.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[...]</dialog>
  <text>Li Sushang looked at the towering man and held her ground.</text>
  <dialog chara="008">[Aye, it’d be way easier if you just killed him]</dialog>
  <text>Ma Feima shrugged.</text>
  <dialog chara="008">
    <p>[Fine. If you’re so intent on protecting him… Then I’ll let you start. </p>
    <p>Not ready? I’ll let you take as long as you want to get back to prime condition. </p>
    <p>Remember, fight this battle with the resolve to kill me. I won’t hold back.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[Why do we have to fight?!]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="008">[...]</dialog>
  <text>He stared at her and smiled.</text>
  <text>That’s it. He’d said everything already, so why say anything else? Ma Feima had already decided, and whatever he decided, he will do.</text>
  <text>The girl bit her lip and despite being unsatisfied, complied with his instructions.</text>
  <motion chara="001" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="002" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="008" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="clock" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="心湖（1）止水"></bg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>This wasn’t some common rabble.</p>
    <p>There was very little chance of winning even if she gave her all. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>After all— he was the Sixth Sword of Taixuan, an expert who could rival her master!</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="心湖（2）无尘" duration="3"></bg>
  <mono chara="-3">
    <p></p>
    <p>[em color=#FAFAD2](Aiya, I have to duel again only a couple of days after dueling for the first time in my life?)[/em]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono chara="-3">
    <p></p>
    <p>Even worse, her opponent was one of the strongest seven in these lands …</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true" chara="-3">
    <p></p>
    <p>[em color=#FAFAD2](It’s like the books say. Once you enter these lands, there’s no getting out.)[/em]</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="心湖（3）明镜" duration="3"></bg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Li Sushang felt all of those thoughts flow through her and turned them into her will for fighting.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Her Mind Lake was calm and waveless, it was clean and clear like a mirror.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>This was a state even higher than Ma Feima’s [Still Water]:</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Blade Mantra · Clear Mirror.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="goto" to="13"></event>
</scene>