<scene id="000" title="回忆篇1">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="3" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bgm id="秋恋古道（慢抒情）"></bgm>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>When Li Sushang was born, she weighed only two kin and three Ryo. She had almost the same weight as a single sword</p>
    <p>Those in the mountain villa shook their heads, and his father Li Xin turned to her mother Qin Suyi as he spoke.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>「She won't be able to live.」</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>At that time, Qin Suyi was in the middle of recuperating after childbirth and answered as follows:</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>「Even if she couldn't live, that was her fate.</p>
    <p>I don't hate fate, but we have no intention of having a second child.</p>
    <p>Even if the Lee bloodline ends now, that's fate.」</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>It is said that upon hearing this, Li Xin turned pale and left.</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="忆剑山庄" duration="2"></bg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Thanks to the care of her mother and wet nurse, Li Sushang had survived. And she was still very well-rested as a result...</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <bg img="忆剑山庄门外" duration="2"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>One hundred days after the birth of Sushang, Li Xin invited a famous fortune-teller 「Kohansen」 to her villa.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Kohansen makes a sigil and chants an incantation. After observing her for some time around Sushang, she yelps out loud—</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>「The young lord was born a genius with the talent for swordsmanship. He had an extraordinary fate, and he looked like someone who would do something important!」</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>There were many different interpretations of those words. Overjoyed at what he had expected, Li Xin thought that his daughter would fulfill her dream to stand on top in the martial arts world instead and held a banquet for him—a grand celebration</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>However, there was no main character at the banquet.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Qin Suyi, the real 「Sennin」’s pupil and a cold-eyed stare at that farce before leaving with her daughter in his arms</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>She went back to the bedroom, lowered her daughter onto a soft rug and placed some small wooden swords beside it</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The young Sushang reached out to touch the sword, but she couldn't. Hata Suyi said nothing and simply watched in silence</p>
  </mono>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑" duration="2"></cg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Ever since she was old enough to remember, there had been a sword by Li Sushang’s side. So maybe it wasn't long before the girl learned about her blade</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Her mother had taught her unusual ways of speaking, and his father was teaching each girl the twelve forms that were used to remember swordsmanship.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Thus, Li Sushang spent her childhood training with the sword and four years passed in an instant.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The young Sushang had practiced diligently, and the Denka’s swordplay wasn't bad at all. But even so her mother refused to listen by saying that she would be sent into a vast desert for 「Apprenticeship」</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>In response to this, Sushang cried and screamed but didn't resist much.</p>
    <p>As a young girl, she had no concept of places like Bakuhoku or Nankan and didn't know how to leave home.</p>
  </mono>
  <cg duration="2"></cg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>A few days after it was decided that he would go to the desert, a well-liked Stone Suzuri Dojin from all across Shaanxi visited Omokukenzanso. To welcome his guest of honor with open arms and respect for him, her father ordered Nurse Soumo (a wet nurse), who had been brought into their backyards so she could train in this style...</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The wet nurse can't move her legs the way she wants. Sushang sneaks out of my backyard without being noticed by a nannies, then hid in its usual spot and peeked into our living room with great interest</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="忆剑山庄内" duration="2"></bg>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>「Long time no see, Master Li.」</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <motion chara="010" action="show" pos="center" img="李绅-温柔-标准-远景" duration="2"></motion>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>After exchanging greetings with a smile, Li Xin sat down for tea and left the rest of their conversation to his wife.</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="010" action="move" pos="left" duration="1"></motion>
  <mono>He understands it very well. The reason why this vast Sword Mountain Manor has gained such a high reputation in the martial arts world is not because of him, but rather...</mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="3"></event>
  <motion chara="009" action="show" pos="right" duration="3" img="秦素衣-标准-标准-远景"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <event action="show_ui"></event>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>—His wife, the seventh disciple of 「Celestial Phoenix」 「Somekoken」 Taixuanza Celestial Soi Hata.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>At the time, when Celestial Phoenix was still in this world—if anyone had to say he controlled Shinshu’s martial arts society...it would have been him.</p>
    <p>Legend has it that Phoenix is a Celestial who descended to the world below. Not only does he have immortality, but also his unparalleled talent in martial arts</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>But ten years ago, a golden light suddenly appeared on Mount Taixuan. The Celestial rode the crane to heaven and turned it into scorched earth by an inferno...</p>
    <p>That incident had caused quite a stir in the martial arts world. Everyone wanted to know why a Celestial who’d protected Shinshu for over one thousand years suddenly returned from heaven</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Now that the Celestial were no longer in this world, their answer would naturally lead them to expect much from 「Taixuan Shichiken」—the seven disciples of one</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Keen----</p>
    <p>The elderly monk drank his tea, placed the lid on a chaki (tea utensil), and told him about recent events in martial arts before finally speaking of a Celestial.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>「To be honest, Phoenix-sama saved me when I was young. But even now he regretted not being able to thank him properly... *Sigh* He'll probably come back again someday!」</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-温柔-标准-远景"></motion>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Qin Suyi also put his hand on the tea utensil and answered with a laugh.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>「We mortals don't speculate about the Celestial on our own. As long as we have some connection to them, I believe that they will be reunited with Master Cleric!」</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The monk laughed loudly and nodded, then never spoke of Phoenix again.</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="010" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="009" action="hide"></motion>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>After finishing his tea, the monk announced that he had free time.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Her father saw the customer off, and when she returned he looked gloomy.</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="010" action="show" pos="right" img="李绅-邪笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「What do you think that tanuki dad came here for? He's after our sword fighting spirit.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="show" pos="left" img="秦素衣-冷漠-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「...Ours?」</dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Li Sushang couldn't help but be surprised at the disdain in her mother’s words.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>In her memories, their parents were always on good terms. Yes...just like the other married couples</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>She didn’t know her mother and father talked like that.</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「If he's after 『Tanuki Dad』, then...</p>
    <p>What are you?」</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-标准-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「Me? Suyi, I-I... can swear my feelings for you to the sun and moon.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-温柔-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「Why don't you stop with that? I am no longer the same little girl as back then.」</dialog>
  <text>Qin Suyi said indifferently.</text>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-苦笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「You helped me back then, and you've been very kind to my life. Because of your kindness I thought that it would be a good idea for us both as wives so we could teach each other the true meaning behind swordsmanship—whether this was just lip service or genuine love...」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-冷漠-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「But as time passes, you can see people's hearts. When I failed to master the art of swordplay... what did it say? What have we done for each other up until this point in our lives! Li Xin is a married couple and lies do not work on us at all」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「The fact that you saved me and whispered your love was a lie. I want to get my hands on Taixuan, but it's the only truth in this world!」</dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-冷漠-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「Suyi...」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-苦笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「Oh well, it doesn't matter now. Keep talking!」</dialog>
  <text>His father fell silent for a while.</text>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「You are guilty of being attached to an innocent man. There is fifty thousand people in the martial arts world who seek you after learning Edge of Taixuan, and now they have Phoenix's name; everyone fears that he will be known as The Seven Sword... But from here on out ...」</dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-愤怒-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">
    <p>「...In the end, her imaginary form is fake. It will disappear over time like a scent of ink on paper...</p>
    <p>If your secret is revealed to the martial arts world...」</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「I understand what you're trying to say. Yes, the Swordcracker Mountain Manor cannot protect me and neither can yours...」</dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">
    <p>「Yeah. We're the only ones who know about this, but there is no way to cover up what really happened...</p>
    <p>For example, your disciple... Did you notice his gaze the last time he was here?</p>
    <p>Would you laugh at me for being so suspicious if I said he noticed?」</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <text>As Qin Suyi fell silent, Li Xin continued</text>
  <dialog chara="010">「From what you've told me, I will never be able to master the art of swordsmanship in my entire life. But if it is true that one can learn a full-blown martial arts style with only their bare clothes...」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「You're the one who has high hopes for Sushang.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-温柔-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「Yeah, well... But what about it?」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="010">「That girl is our daughter. She has talent with a sword, and she's blessed to be gifted in the field as well! Why not teach her how takken spirit works?」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="010">「We don't need to send her somewhere that far away. If something happens, we can never stay by your side...」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-冷漠-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「And as for that fifth disciple... Is there a reason why I have to send her Sushang?!」</dialog>
  <text>Waiting for him to finish, Qin Suyi opened his mouth.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「Taixuan has five elements.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-标准-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「...Hm?」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-厌恶-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「The heart, the shape of it all: will. Souls and gods—you should know what a sword looks like as well</p>
    <p>After that, I didn't talk about it until now and thought there was no need to.」</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>Qin Suyi snorted contemptuously.</text>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-温柔-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「Hmph. I wasn't trying to hide it from you or anything, but there is no point in talking about the Three Uninvolved Wisdom Clan members when they cannot even master a sword heart!」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「Kenshin is the foundation of a Taixuan school, and swordsmanship as an introductory to “Taixuani”... Those are things that we seven have mastered.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-恍然-标准-中景"></motion>
  <text>The coldness in her mother’s voice diminished, replaced by more ephemerality.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「My 『Sumizomeka』, that mysterious power... is the will of swordsmanship. Master gave us all a penchant for wielding kenjou-tsurugi! The shape changes when we realize our intentions are different from each other」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「Out of the seven, only my fifth disciple Lingshuang-neechan was able to learn his will. After all... she doesn't need it anymore!」</dialog>
  <text>Her mother fell silent for a while, as if basking in memories.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「Swordsmanship is the essence of swordplay.</p>
    <p>The way of the sword was all creation in Morira, and it itself had been nothing more than a possession.」</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-贪婪-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「After learning Soul Un, you can use every weapon in the world like a sword and no longer have to worry about its shape.</p>
    <p>Only when he reached that boundary could his swordplay be said to have achieved great feats.」</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="010">「Using all kinds of weapons like swords...」</dialog>
  <text>Li Xin couldn't help but be startled.</text>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-邪笑-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="010">「Taixuan, that's the taiky sword ki for you! It really is a divine technique.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-冷漠-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「Yes.」</dialog>
  <text>Qin Suyi’s ephemerality vanished as if waking from a dream, and his tone returned to its original cold one.</text>
  <motion chara="010" action="img_trans" img="李绅-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「However, there is a divine spirit above the soul.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-阴沉-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「The God----Without technique, the Swordless will win against Ariken. Their swordsmanship can turn into a blade with only their hearts and minds as they wish it to be! That is what this god of war means...」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「Only five thousand years have passed since I learned the Divine Vow. Even among us eight, only Master and Lingshuang-neechan are able to reach a boundary between Sword Godsmen!」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-厌恶-标准-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「My master is a Celestial, so it's not strange at all. But Lingshuang was able to obtain the supremely powerful Sword God in her mortal body... Heheh! I admire that talent from my heart and soul.」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「That's why...」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="010" action="hide"></motion>
  <text>Through a small hole in the window, young Sushang saw her mother slowly walking before his father.</text>
  <motion chara="009" action="show" pos="left" img="秦素衣-阴沉-标准-远景" duration="2"></motion>
  <motion chara="010" action="show" pos="center" img="李绅-愤怒-标准-远景" duration="2"></motion>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <dialog chara="009">「I'll have to take her under my wing. No one but Lingshuang would be a good match for me!」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「The best swordsmanship you can learn from the strongest wielder of a real blade. With learning Sword God and adding my henken to it, she will be your only one who has learned Taixuan Wuyun after her master died!」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-温柔-标准-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="009">「I'm going to have you become the best in all of Japan.」</dialog>
  <text>Li Sushang couldn't help but gasp. Her heart pounded in her chest</text>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「If you need ten years, I'll have Bakuhoku stay here for 10.</p>
    <p>If you need twenty years, I'll have them stay for 20.」</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="img_trans" img="秦素衣-厌恶-标准-远景"></motion>
  <text>The mother stared at her father. There was a firmness in his eyes that didn't allow him to object</text>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「Don't think I can keep Sushang locked away in your Swordcracker Manor. This is not the extent of her talent, you know?</p>
    <p>Anyway, get away from Sushang. Don't interfere with my daughters life!」</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">「Who was responsible for returning to the Li family, and who could have obtained their current martial arts? Please don't forget that.」</dialog>
  <motion chara="009" action="move" pos="-1500,0" duration="3"></motion>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>With that, her mother left the living room.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Li Xin stood rooted to the spot, motionless for a long time. A sound came from her clenched fist</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Sushang was sitting there in a daze. It surprised me, but it also made my heart race with joy...</p>
  </mono>
  <motion chara="009" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="010" action="hide"></motion>
  <bg duration="2" img="忆剑山庄"></bg>
  <dialog chara="002">（The best in the world...?）</dialog>
  <text inline="true">She hadn’t realized that her mother was expecting this much from herself.</text>
  <text>Perhaps it was just a whim of her mother. But though she hadn't made this clear yet, the light that stretched far and wide into the young girl’s heart shone through</text>
  <dialog chara="002">（Am I... going to be the best in this world?）</dialog>
  <text>She swallowed and rubbed her eyes. Just as she was about to stand up, I saw a white figure</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <cg img="CG_回忆篇_李素裳" duration="2"></cg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <text inline="true">I looked up and saw Qin Suyi, the owner of Omokuken Mountain Manor.</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>Her mother smiled, but there was sadness and apology in her eyes.</p>
  </text>
  <dialog chara="009">「Did you hear everything?」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">「Yeah...」</dialog>
  <text>Sushang was so full of impulse that I wanted to tell my mother she would never let me down. But the words came out at her throat, and ultimately didn't say anything about it...</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「I'm sorry.」</dialog>
  <text>Her mother crouched down and gently patted her head.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「I'm so sorry for sending you to such a faraway place, even though your mother is still young... But my mom will make arrangements. In the future when that sword reaches its zenith no one can bully us anymore!」</dialog>
  <dialog chara="009">
    <p>「Mom has her own problems to deal with. Even if I tell you now, she won't understand me at all...</p>
    <p>When I'm in the martial arts world, there are a lot of things that can never be decided by me. But...</p>
    <p>I'm going to live. Sushang, you will be living properly... Promises with my mother!」</p>
  </dialog>
  <text>The young Sushang looked into her mother’s eyes and nodded, faltering.</text>
  <text>
    <p>She still didn't understand everything her mother said, and could only read a portion of the emotion.</p>
    <p>Even so, he realized that a burden which shouldn’t have existed at his age rested on him.</p>
  </text>
  <notification>伝記解放：「秦素衣」</notification>
  <notification>伝記解放：「李紳」</notification>
  <event action="achievement" aid="f264952df7ffa72c"></event>
  <event action="achievement" aid="2e4bba1abf781c9f"></event>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <cg duration="2"></cg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <text>Qin Suyi took the young Sushang's hand and smiled gently.</text>
  <dialog chara="009">「Come here, there's something I want to give you.」</dialog>
  <transition mode="fade" in="3" stop="0.5" out="0.1" color="#000000"></transition>
</scene>
scripts>