<scene id="22" prev="21" title="終わり">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="3" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="入云阶" pos="0,-600" duration="3"></bg>
  <bgm id="天穹"></bgm>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Heaven’s Pinnacle, Cloud Strider Stairway.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="10"></event>
  <bg img="入云阶" duration="10" pos="0,0"></bg>
  <delay t="10"></delay>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Heaven’s Pinnacle towers over the sky, the mountain’s steps stretching over a thousand feet.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Looking up, you couldn’t see the end of the stone stairs, only misty clouds hanging up with a glance.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="5"></event>
  <bg img="天穹峰顶-外景" duration="5" scale="2" origin="80%,50%"></bg>
  <delay t="4"></delay>
  <bg img="天穹峰顶-外景" duration="7" origin="80%,50%"></bg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>The mountain is a high mountain; on top of this mountain, is also a high person. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>After climbing several thousand stone steps, I saw a small pathetic view called 「Kumo」 at the top of its peak.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="6"></event>
  <bg img="拂云观-侧面" duration="10"></bg>
  <delay t="6"></delay>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Regardless of name, shape, or furnishings, this Fog Mount Temple was an exact replica of the former Celestial Phoenix’s abode on Mount Taixuan.</p>
    <p>The master of this temple,</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Was the Head of one of the Six Great Sects of Shenzhou [School of Taixuan];</p>
    <p>Phoenix’s eldest disciple: [Willowfoil] Lin Zhaoyu.</p>
    <p>…The Head is very quiet, plus the road was both long and arduous;</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>If the disciples of the School of Taixuan don’t have anything to do, they will never ascend the Cloud Strider Stairway. </p>
    <p>Therefore, this day should’ve been an average day, a quiet and ordinary day.</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Knock, knock, knock.</p>
  </mono>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <se id="01-70敲门声" looptimes="3"></se>
  <text>[em delay=1] Knock, [/em][em delay=1] Knock, [/em][em delay=0.5] Knock.[/em]</text>
  <text>Now there’s an uninvited guest, who knocked on Fog Mount Temple’s door with a smile. </text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="004" action="show" pos="center" img="苏湄-自信-标准-中景（带武器）" duration="1"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>This person is wearing a bold and easy-to-move suit, carrying twin yin-yang swords, born with vermillion hair and a jade-like face, and looks very beautiful.</text>
  <text>
    <p>Although she rarely walked around in the Jianghu Society, she and her disciples acted at a low profile;[\s]</p>
    <p>But the name of this person was almost as prominent as the Heads and Elders of the Six Great Sects.</p>
  </text>
  <notification>伝記解放：「蘇湄」</notification>
  <event action="achievement" aid="809d736ce396e092"></event>
  <text>
    <p>She is Phoenix’s second disciple, the current master of [Ushuang’s Hall],[\s]</p>
    <p>[Ushuang Exarch] ——Su Mei.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="004" action="hide"></motion>
  <bg img="拂云观-侧面" scale="1.5" origin="0%,50%" duration="3"></bg>
  <se id="01-70敲门声"></se>
  <text>Knock.</text>
  <bg img="拂云观-侧面" duration="1" origin="0%,50%"></bg>
  <text>Her knuckles tapped on the wooden door lightly, the sound loud and undisturbed, it was slightly crisp and nice.</text>
  <motion chara="004" action="show" pos="right" img="苏湄-标准-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <text>There wasn’t a response from the room, yet the red haired woman wasn’t angry, her face’s smile continued to be calm.</text>
  <se id="01-70敲门声2"></se>
  <text>Knock, knock.</text>
  <motion chara="004" action="hide" duration="0"></motion>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="3"></event>
  <se id="01-71开门声"></se>
  <bg img="拂云观-侧面（开门）" duration="3"></bg>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <text>Finally, the door opened.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="4"></event>
  <bg img="拂云观-亮" duration="1"></bg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <motion chara="003" action="show" pos="center" duration="3" img="林朝雨-不悦-标准-中景"></motion>
  <delay t="3"></delay>
  <text>
    <p>As if she was unaware of the knocker’s long wait, </p>
    <p>[Willowfoil] Lin Zhaoyu walked out of the house slowly, staring coldly at her former Second Junior Sister.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <bg img="拂云观-侧面（开门）" duration="1"></bg>
  <motion chara="003" action="show" pos="left" img="林朝雨-标准-标准-远景"></motion>
  <motion chara="004" action="show" pos="right" img="苏湄-甜笑-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <notification>伝記解放：「林朝雨」</notification>
  <event action="achievement" aid="fcf2a1388f09b18b"></event>
  <dialog chara="004">[Senior Sister, how long has it been since you’ve seen me?]</dialog>
  <text>Su Mei smiled enthusiastically, as if she was reuniting with a long lost best friend after many years. [\s]Although there are thousands of smiling faces in the world, this is the only one that Lin Zhaoyu doesn’t know how to deal with.</text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-认真-标准-远景"></motion>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-平静-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[...Twenty years.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="004">[Twenty years?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-标准-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <text>[Ushuang] Su Mei thought for a bit, before casually smiling:</text>
  <dialog chara="004">[It’s been that long?]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>Her voice’s sound floated into Lin Zhaoyu’s ears, like a thin needle stuck in her heart. </p>
    <p>She couldn’t help but glance at the woman in front of her with contempt.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="hide"></motion>
  <motion chara="004" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="dissolve" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <motion chara="004" action="show" pos="center" img="苏湄-标准-标准-近景"></motion>
  <text>Over ten years had passed, yet Su Mei hadn't changed at all, and time seemed to have stopped for her.</text>
  <text inline="true">Her hair was still red and vibrant,</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>Her beautiful face was shiny and smooth as fat, it could be broken by a blow.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Her eyes… the eyes were still so big, so alluring… </p>
    <p>Her lips are so red, so red… this vixen, how many sheets of rouge paper did she use?</p>
  </text>
  <text>[em color=#FAFAD2 italic]… …Why was it her? Why wasn’t it me?[/em]</text>
  <motion chara="004" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="eye" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="拂云观-侧面（开门）"></bg>
  <motion chara="003" action="show" pos="left" img="林朝雨-愤恨-标准-远景"></motion>
  <motion chara="004" action="show" pos="right" img="苏湄-标准-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <text>Envy filled Lin Zhaoyu’s heart in an instant, it boiled extremely quickly, and it froze; it was hot like ice, it was cold like fire.</text>
  <text>Su Mei seemed to see through her thoughts, and let out a sigh at this moment.</text>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-闭目-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-标准-标准-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[Aye, twenty years, I’ve aged too.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">[...Really.]</dialog>
  <text>The Head of the School of Taixuan replied softly.</text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-认真-标准-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[No need to reminisce, you and I don’t need to chat, just speak if you have something to say.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-瞥视-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[Mm, that’s fine too.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-平静-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <text>A trace of haze seemed to pass over Su Mei’s eyes, it was fleeting, causing Lin Zhaoyu to catch a glimpse of worry in her eyes.</text>
  <dialog chara="004">[...The reason I came to visit my Senior Sister, is because Little Ma got a message.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-惊讶-标准-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[Yanqing?]</dialog>
  <text>Lin Zhaoyu’s face changed quickly, and sharply said:</text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤怒-标准-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[Where is he?]</dialog>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The name Little Ma that came from Su Mei’s mouth, was the two people’s Junior Brother [Tireless Courser] Ma Yanqing. [\s]</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>This Taixuan Sixth Sword had an arrogant temperament, and he had never been restrained by the world;</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>This person had a close relationship with [Ushuang] Su Mei, and he was envied by everyone in the Jianghu Society. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Yet he suddenly announced that he would marry a Senior Sister who was more than twenty years older than him, which shook the Jianghu;</p>
    <p></p>
    <p>On the day of the wedding, he was drunk and nonsensical. He was ashamed of his name and abandoned it, which embarrassed all the guests.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Even after getting married, he rarely appeared in the School of Taixuan for a while. </p>
    <p></p>
    <p>For most of the year, he and his beloved horse [Erebus] wandered around. What he did that was good to hear was said to be [fighting for justice and chivalry], and the ugly, said to be [misbehavior]. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Whether up to the rich and the powerful, or down to bandits… Ma Feima dared to beat anyone, and everyone who provoked him. This [Madman], is indeed the most famous character in the Central Plains. </p>
  </mono>
  <dialog chara="004">
    <p>[Yanqing… Little Ma hates that name very much. </p>
    <p>Yet Senior Sister hasn’t changed her words yet… Alas, Senior Sister is the most nostalgic among us.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤恨-标准-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>[em color=#FAFAD2 italic]No…[/em]</p>
    <p>Lin Zhaoyu said in her heart.</p>
    <p>[em color=#FAFAD2 italic]What he hates is the past, which is specifically the past YOU created.[/em]</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>Her thoughts sank into her heart, and the sound was no more.</p>
    <p>She also didn’t resort to words.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-不悦-标准-远景"></motion>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-闭目-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[Where is he?]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>Lin Zhaoyu repeated.[\s]</p>
    <p>Su Mei met her gaze quickly and looked away, then sighed:</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-瞥视-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[You know Little Ma’s temperament… he already rushed to the Northern Desert overnight.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">[Beyond the Great Wall? …What’s he going to do there?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="004">[To look for Fifth Junior Sister.]</dialog>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤恨-标准-远景"></motion>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-标准-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[——! ! !]</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤恨-持剑-远景" duration="1"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-瞥视-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>Fiery anger suddenly melted the ice.</p>
    <p>Lin Zhaoyu took a big step forward, and silently slipped a silver longsword into her left hand.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-冷笑-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">
    <p>[Su Mei… What the hell are you plotting now? </p>
    <p>It’s been 20 years, do you think we’ll be fooled by you again?!]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤恨-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">
    <p>[Lingshuang’s secluded whereabouts, did you think Yanqing and I don’t know? </p>
    <p>When she grabbed a Xuanyuan and wandered all over the Central Plains, causing trouble out in the limelight, during that time, who was it who got her out of Southern Hunan? </p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">Who was it who secretly protected her on her way to the Northern Desert and helped her settle?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">
    <p>[Yanqing’s temperament… heh, I know Yanqing's character, I also know Lingshuang’s temperament. </p>
    <p>Even if the sky fell tomorrow, he won’t disturb Lingshuang with such trivial things or disturb her hermitage. </p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">So what? Could you tell me what news is so important, that Yanqing couldn’t even spare the time to tell me?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="004">「……」</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-冷笑-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[...It’s still this means, Su Mei, it’s still this. Yanqing is willing to listen to your words,『Little Ma』...hmph. </dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">What about you? You call him at will, pointing east to east, pointing west to west… Who do you take my husband for? Who do you take ME for?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤怒-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">
    <p>[Su Mei, I’m warning you today.</p>
    <p>If you no longer treasure shared sect comradery in your heart,</p>
    <p>Then I won’t hesitate to fight『Ushuang』!]</p>
  </dialog>
  <dialog chara="004">「……」</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-愤恨-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>All of the buried words that’ve been accumulating for years were reprimanded, yet she felt unhappy. </p>
    <p>Lin Zhaoyu was satisfied with the silence from the other party, but she was also surprised about that silence.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>The wind’s sound whistled, the piercing cold hovered on top of Heaven’s Pinnacle. </p>
    <p>This kind of weather could either fan the flames of rage, or slowly let it smolder until only the ashes of disappointment remained. </p>
  </text>
  <text>After she counted her seventeenth heartbeat, when her patience was about to come to an end, Su Mei spoke up.</text>
  <bgm id="千年之羽"></bgm>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-闭目-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[『Willowfoil』...]</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-惊讶-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>Su Mei didn’t look at her, rather her gaze fixedly fell upon the soft sword in her hand.</text>
  <dialog chara="004">
    <p>[It’s really nostalgic…</p>
    <p>Thanks to it, Wanru could keep her life, and it gave Fifth Junior Sister a moment to stab with that sword.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-自信-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <text>She lifted her head to meet Lin Zhaoyu’s gaze, her eyebrows raised into a smile:</text>
  <dialog chara="004">[Very good, it’s still in your hands.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-惊恐-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[You——]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>At the mention of that day twenty years ago, Lin Zhaoyu subconsciously took a step back.[\s]</p>
    <p>The cold air condensed to dew on her back, turning into cold sweat under her robes.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-怅然-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>
    <p>For many years, the scene of that time had been torturing her like bone decay.</p>
    <p>She thought she had finally left her past behind, but the visit from her Second Sister today has reopened her old scar.</p>
    <p>[We promised to never talk about the old days——]</p>
  </text>
  <dialog chara="003">[Mm. I’m not talking about the old stuff, because the past is gone, and remembering it is useless.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-闭目-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[So, I’m talking about something new.]</dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-平静-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[...Oh!?]</dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-惊恐-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">Lin Zhaoyu was taken aback, and instantly understood the profound meaning of her Junior Sister’s words.</dialog>
  <text>[S-so… you’re saying, Master s-she’s?]</text>
  <dialog chara="003">[Mm.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="004">Su Mei looked up at the sky, as if she noticed something interesting in the air, and had an indiscernible smile. </dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-微笑-别过-远景（带武器）" duration="0.5"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>[Our Xuanyuan Swords are about to be unsheathed again. But if my guess is right… mine will be earlier than yours.]</text>
  <dialog chara="004">[This… you, impossible… </dialog>
  <dialog chara="003">this…]</dialog>
  <text>For the first time in 20 years, the School of Taixuan’s female head showed such a flustered expression. </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-怅然-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[...Master’s dead.]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="004">
    <p>[Right, but does death exist to a Celestial? Trust me, Master has returned. </p>
    <p>You, me, Little Ma… none of us seven should want to stay out of this matter.]</p>
  </dialog>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-惊恐-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[...No…]</dialog>
  <text>Lin Zhaoyu looked down in a daze, as if the other party was just saying extremely absurd gossip that wasn’t worth listening to.</text>
  <dialog chara="003">[But… If…]</dialog>
  <text>Her murmurs became weaker.</text>
  <text>
    <p>When she lifted her head at Su Mei again, a smile hung on Lin Zhaoyu’s face. </p>
    <p>It was an extremely angry smile, yet it was also an extremely weary smile.</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-怒笑-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="003">[If Master is to settle out the score years ago, the first one to look for is you, Su Mei.]</dialog>
  <text>School of Taixuan’s female head spoke softly. </text>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-痛苦-别过-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <dialog chara="004">[Wrong, wrong, Master doesn’t know who the mastermind is. According to inference, I’m still the second one~ But, the order isn’t important. I came to find you for this.] </dialog>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-平静-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <motion chara="003" action="img_trans" img="林朝雨-心头一震-持剑-远景"></motion>
  <text>She turned her look away from the clouds and gazed at Lin Zhaoyu.</text>
  <text>
    <p>Lin Zhaoyu was shocked.[\s]</p>
    <p>This was what she was very familiar with, her Second Junior Sister’s look in her eyes.</p>
  </text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <motion chara="004" action="img_trans" img="苏湄-标准-标准-远景（带武器）"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>Su Mei was calmly looking at her, collected and composed. Her eyes showed neither fear, nor panic. </text>
  <dialog chara="004">[Master has already killed one.]  </dialog>
  <transition mode="fade" in="5" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
</scene>