<scene id="14" prev="13" title="月下の剣舞">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bgm id="原始武士"></bgm>
  <bg img="废弃驿站院内" duration="2"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" pos="center" img="老鹰-普通-叉腰-远景" duration="2"></motion>
  <text>It was deep into the night, yet “Eagle” wasn’t tired.</text>
  <text>The parlor of the dilapidated Stop was brightly lit, making the light and shadows divide the yard outside of the hall split to two. </text>
  <text>“Eagle” stood in the yard. His eight most trusted subordinates stood nearby, watching him sword dancing.  </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="move" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000" direction="left" custom="default"></transition>
  <bg img="废弃驿站"></bg>
  <text>“Eagle” was no swordsman, nor was he proficient in swordsmanship. He was once a member of the military, and learned greatsword techniques. </text>
  <text>
    <p>Sword and greatsword techniques appear the same, but they're in fact completely different.</p>
    <p>As people say [Swords are quick, greatswords are strong.] Swords travel with trickery, flexible yet varying; greatswords are fair, breaking through with power. </p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>When a sword wielder is given a greatsword, they will use it like a sword, the same is vice versa. </p>
    <p>Therefore, although “Eagle” was sword dancing, he was actually greatsword dancing.</p>
  </text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" img="老鹰-狞笑-拔刀预备-近景" duration="2" pos="center"></motion>
  <text inline="true">The reason why he has the sword, is also because the sword is really satisfying.</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>He had never seen such a perfect blade!</p>
  </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="move" in="0.5" stop="0.2" out="0.5" color="#000000" direction="left" custom="thick"></transition>
  <bg img="轩辕剑-横行" pos="-1020,0"></bg>
  <se id="01-18男性沙漠疾行_01"></se>
  <delay t="0.1"></delay>
  <bg img="轩辕剑-横行" duration="40" pos="0,0"></bg>
  <text>“Eagle” hauled the sword in his hand, his movement swift. Suddenly his wrist quivered, and three sword flowers bloomed.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <se id="01-49舞剑"></se>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text inline="true">It seemed to be like an ink filled brush. Wherever the sword went, dark gray lines were left behind in the air, like freehand calligraphy. </text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>This was exactly like the beauty of the sword’s patterns, very gratifying.</p>
  </text>
  <se id="01-27大刀横挥"></se>
  <text inline="true">“Eagle” stabbed sharply with the sword, and pulled out the strength from his wrist. The sword’s body didn’t move, yet the sword edge seemed to quiver slightly, singing with the sound of a soft hum. </text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>This fit the firmness of the sword’s body, sturdiness and softness.</p>
  </text>
  <se id="01-21轩辕剑氛围声"></se>
  <cg></cg>
  <text inline="true">When the sword was retracted, it slowed for a moment again. When the blade reached the chest, the edge was cool, and the light shined.</text>
  <text>
    <p></p>
    <p>This was exactly what the sword’s shine was like, the cold light penetrated through bones. </p>
  </text>
  <se id="01-21轩辕剑氛围声" looptimes="0"></se>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="废弃驿站院内" duration="1"></bg>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" img="老鹰-狞笑-拔刀预备-近景" pos="center" duration="2"></motion>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <text>“Eagle” couldn’t help but laugh heartily, and he pulled out a string of hair and held it above the blade. When he let it go, the hair split to two. </text>
  <text>This is just how acute the sword is: so sharp that it would cut falling hair.</text>
  <text>If it has the four aforementioned traits, this sword could be considered as legendary. </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="img_trans" img="老鹰-专注-拔刀预备-近景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[Priceless, priceless…]</dialog>
  <text>“Eagle” murmured. </text>
  <motion chara="015" action="hide"></motion>
  <transition mode="move" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000" direction="left" custom="default"></transition>
  <bg img="废弃驿站"></bg>
  <text>
    <p>“Eagle” isn’t a sword lover or collector. </p>
    <p>Even if he speaks words of praise, it’s nothing more than just a bandit admiring his spoils. </p>
  </text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="1"></event>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑" scale="1.5" origin="80%,0%"></cg>
  <delay t="1"></delay>
  <cg img="氛围_通用_轩辕剑" duration="10" scale="1.5" pos="400,-200" origin="80%,0%"></cg>
  <text>A person who knows goods well would be able to tell that this sword on the girl’s body is worth more than silver or gold.</text>
  <text inline="true">But he was still a warrior. </text>
  <text>Famous swords were like beautiful jades since ancient times, and whoever wins it would be admired.</text>
  <text>“Eagle” decided to keep it. Not because it had anything to do with gold or silver, but rather as a symbol of status.</text>
  <text>After all, a figure like him, should have a weapon that matches.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <cg img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰笑" scale="2.5" origin="15%,0%"></cg>
  <text>As the Golden Sand Gang examined Li Sushang’s『Xuanyuan』from left to right, the more gratified he became.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Do you like my sword that much?]</dialog>
  <cg img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李抱胸" scale="2.5" origin="15%,0%"></cg>
  <dialog chara="015">[! ! ! ! !]</dialog>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <cg duration="2" img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李抱胸" origin="15%,0%"></cg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <text>“Eagle” was shocked, and instinctively backed away six feet.</text>
  <text>
    <p>He couldn’t believe the scene in front of his eyes.[\s]</p>
    <p>Eight men were lying on the ground, all unconscious. </p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>And the girl that he ordered to be taken to the Dark Dungeon, was blinking at him.[\s]</p>
    <p>[em italic]WHAT HAPPENED!?!?[/em]</p>
  </text>
  <text>…If this is a joke, he would cut the mastermind into pieces, and feed them to a horse.</text>
  <cg img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李伸手" duration="2"></cg>
  <text>But the girl appeared fearless, stretching her hands:</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Hey, you’ve played enough with it, so it’s time to give it back to me now.] </dialog>
  <dialog chara="015">「...Don't be ridiculous!」</dialog>
  <text>“Eagle” was already distraught, but the girl’s dialogue made him even more irritated.</text>
  <text>He doesn’t like the feeling of being confused about the circumstances, and he wanted to regain control of the situation.</text>
  <dialog chara="015">[...How did you escape?]</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[Oh, it was a Raksha who helped me out… Eh, where did he go?]</dialog>
  <cg img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李普通_呆滞" duration="2"></cg>
  <text>The girl turned her head, her back, and looked around.</text>
  <dialog chara="015">[※※, damn that Raksha!]</dialog>
  <cg duration="2" img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李普通_呆滞"></cg>
  <text>
    <p>“Eagle” cursed at himself viciously in his mind.[\s]</p>
    <p>If you were aware of a『hazard』, then it would be better to get rid of it as soon as possible.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>It’s precisely because he was afraid of these hazards, that hazards often cause problems.[\s]</p>
    <p>“Eagle” regretted not paying attention to the strange Raksha, but at this moment, regret was no longer helpful.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>He stepped back quietly, forming a safe distance for dialogue. This was actually unnecessary, because he was the one holding the sword.[\s]</p>
    <p>…But, it wasn’t the girl Eagle was worried about.</p>
  </text>
  <text>At this moment, the moon shines brightly. The shadows reflected by the throbbing candlelight danced wildly on the bluestone floor, and it was a good time to solve the problem. </text>
  <dialog chara="015">[What about that Raksha? …Where is he?]</dialog>
  <cg duration="2" img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李伸手"></cg>
  <dialog chara="002">[I don’t know.]</dialog>
  <text>The girl was telling the truth, she seemed to not know what lies were. </text>
  <motion chara="002" action="img_trans" img="素裳-专注-抱手-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="002">[He was behind me, but he suddenly disappeared.]</dialog>
  <text>This truly is the worst answer.[\s]In fact, “Eagle” didn’t pay attention to the girl at all. [\s]No matter how good an opponent’s martial arts is, it was impossible for him to lose to such a straightforward kid. </text>
  <text>
    <p>From the beginning to the end, he regarded that Raksha as his biggest threat. </p>
    <p>And being unable to grasp that person’s movements made him anxious. </p>
  </text>
  <text>The Raksha may have disappeared faraway, or may be hiding somewhere just waiting for an opportunity— but no matter what it was, a thorn was always in his heart. He wouldn’t feel at ease until he took him out.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[Hey, don’t look for him, your opponent right now is me.]</dialog>
  <cg duration="2" img="CG_第一折_鹰李对峙_鹰惊李抱拳_哼"></cg>
  <text>The girl retracted her outstretched hand, her palm was over her fist.</text>
  <dialog chara="002">[I’m gonna take my sword back now~ Eldest Disciple of Wanderer’s House Li Sushang, please enlighten me!]</dialog>
  <bgm looptimes="0"></bgm>
  <text>Her words she spoke were inappropriate for the present moment, making a strange pose anyways.</text>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <se id="01-30女孩轻功whoosh_02"></se>
  <cg img="CG_第一折_起手姿势_1" duration="2" scale="1.2"></cg>
  <text>Before “Eagle” could react, the girl suddenly appeared in front of him. </text>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.1" range="1000" direction="vertical"></motion>
  <cg duration="0"></cg>
  <se id="01-28胸口命中"></se>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.1" range="50" direction="default"></motion>
  <delay t="0.7"></delay>
  <se id="01-40轩辕剑掉落声"></se>
  <bgm id="传奇诞生"></bgm>
  <text>Quicker than words could tell, he felt pain in his forearm, and the sword dropped from his hand. </text>
  <dialog chara="015">[You—]</dialog>
  <se id="01-23腿部命中"></se>
  <motion chara="-4" action="shake" duration="0.1" range="50" direction="default"></motion>
  <text>He took another palm to the chest.</text>
  <text>“Eagle” staggered back a few steps, hurriedly adjusting his breath, but his inner organs were scrambling endlessly, and it was difficult to calm down.</text>
  <bg img="废弃驿站院内" duration="0.5"></bg>
  <motion chara="015" action="show" pos="center" img="老鹰-惊讶-肉搏备战-中景"></motion>
  <dialog chara="015">[...You!]</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>This palm wasn’t powered by internal force, though it was heavy, since it didn’t hurt the internal organs after all. </p>
    <p>But the girl’s light handed agility was something “Eagle” rarely saw.</p>
  </text>
  <text>
    <p>“Eagle” was shocked, left the Raksha behind in his mind, </p>
    <p>and decided to re-evaluate this opponent who was between ten to twenty years old.</p>
  </text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="0" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="15"></event>
</scene>