<scene id="16" prev="15" title="一撃に返す•壱">
  <transition mode="fade" in="0" stop="0.5" out="2" color="#000000"></transition>
  <bg img="心湖（1）止水"></bg>
  <bgm id="侠女之声（女抒情）"></bgm>
  <mono chara="009">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Live well.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The voice echoed in Li Sushang's Mind Lake. </p>
    <p>The lake was calm as usual, everything around was Still Water.</p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <bg img="心湖（2）无尘" duration="2"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <mono chara="009">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Make sure you live well.]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The voice reverberated within the Mind Lake. </p>
    <p>A soft breeze caressed the body, everything was Dustless. </p>
  </mono>
  <event action="hide_ui" duration="2"></event>
  <bg img="心湖（3）明镜" duration="2"></bg>
  <delay t="2"></delay>
  <mono chara="009">
    <p></p>
    <p>[Promise me…]</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>The sound… reverberates. </p>
    <p>The Mind Lake is like a Clear Mirror, illuminating all of heaven and earth.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Why did Blade Sanction fail? No more doubts. [\s]</p>
    <p>Why did Blade Sanction fail? No more regrets. [\s]</p>
    <p>Why did Blade Sanction fail? No more worries.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Throw away all the troubles, just concentrate on this strike. [\s]</p>
    <p>Use the sword— the tool for killing,[\s]</p>
    <p>With sword techniques—  the skills of killing.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>Kill the enemy and live. </p>
    <p>Sushang's thoughts are nothing more than that.</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="PureBlack"></bg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p></p>
    <p>How ironic, the purpose was so simple. [\s]</p>
    <p>Yet she detoured a long, long way.</p>
  </mono>
  <bg img="轩辕剑_灯光00%"></bg>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Holding the hilt with her fingers, she felt relieved. </p>
    <p>This ancient sword Xuanyuan was her only support at the moment.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>Wiping off the blood from the corner of her eye and wiping off the foam from her mouth. </p>
    <p>The girl held a sword in her hand. </p>
    <p>She didn’t rake up any sword stances yet, but, </p>
  </mono>
  <mono>
    <p></p>
    <p>Opening, Switch, Guard, Wrath. </p>
  </mono>
  <mono>Odious Crescent, [\s]Ocean Breaker, [\s]Onslaught.</mono>
  <mono>
    <p>Sailing Eagle, Soaring Falcon, [\s]Raining Swift, Sparrow’s Roost, [\s]Shadow Hawk, Selene’s Heron. [\s]</p>
    <p>Gaunt Willow, Gentle Orchid, Girded Bamboo, [\s]Gray Chrysanthemum, Gleaming Lotus, Green Pines.[\s]</p>
    <p>Ripstone, Roaring Thunder, Railing Blitz, Rockslide, Riven Dust, Roiling Gale.</p>
  </mono>
  <mono pageend="true">
    <p></p>
    <p>These are the four forms and twenty-one stances of Taixuan’s Blade Form. Their names flashed across her mind as the muscle memories of each form passed through her body. </p>
  </mono>
  <dialog chara="008">[Listen.]</dialog>
  <text>Although the enemy was close, the sound seems to be coming from far, far away.</text>
  <dialog chara="008">“I will only use one trick: Wrath Form • Rockslide.”</dialog>
  <dialog chara="002">[……]</dialog>
  <text>Li Sushang remained silent.</text>
  <dialog chara="008">"There is only one move: Wrath Form • Rockslide. I won't keep my hand, let me see your response."</dialog>
  <text>
    <p>Should I apply? </p>
    <p>Ma Feima's instructions slipped through Sushang's mind, and she didn't care.</p>
  </text>
  <text>After all, everything comes down to this one strike.</text>
  <transition mode="fade" in="1" stop="0.5" out="1" color="#000000"></transition>
  <event action="goto" to="17"></event>
</scene>