<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_12_mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="11_12_newChapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="chileRiverMountain.jpg">
            <bgm src="seaAndSky.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>Bianka Ataegina and Rita Rossweisse woke up to the 18th day of their adventure inside the Sea of Quanta.</text>
            <text>The waves were hitting the coast of Chile on this blessed sunny day.</text>
            <text remark="next">At sunrise, the Chairwoman of the Republic arrived at the military port of Chiloé Island, ready to personally welcome the crew of the “Caledonia” who rescued the “Star Whisperer” Sanada Yukimura from Rapa Nui Island.</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX18G7vQ4I8K1+0Z6qTT+">
                <p class="article-text-h">注：</p>
                <p class="article-text">奇洛埃岛（Isla de Chiloé，意为“海鸥之地”）是智利东南部的一座岛屿，地属南温带，气候、风光均与北欧类似。</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. 据考证，奇洛埃岛为马铃薯的主要原产地之一。</p>
            </remark>
            <text>Before the red haired captain’s submarine arrived, the Chairwoman was taking a relaxed walk on the beach with her pet groundhog.</text>
            <text>At that time, most people wouldn’t yet be aware--</text>
            <text>But a plan about to change the world was about to commence in the shadows.</text>
            <goto goto="20" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="palaceMeetingQuito.jpg">
            <bgm src="legion.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>Four days ago, Quito, office of the Republic’s Chairwoman--</text>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">...But instead going into the details, I’ll start with the conclusion.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Facing the threat of Honkai, the Republic has long since developed a plan to completely save the world.</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">It’s a very bold plan with almost no shortcomings--</speak>
            <show chara="thorSighClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">--Except for the lack of someone who can accomplish it.</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">But of course, that changed now. Fate has brought you to the Republic.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Now the preface is over. To be precise, there is a role we want you to take--</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">--The “World Cutter”.</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Your Captain Shakespeare seems to plan to use the gems of “Durindana” to cut the barrier of Honkai Energy.</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">What we want to do is essentially the same--</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">--It just magnifies the target of destruction to being the “world” itself.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">…”Destroy the world itself”? Do you mean it literally?</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">I do.</speak>
            <goto goto="30" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="fractalWorld.jpg">
            <bgm src="bigTask.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">The first step is to use your “Holy Sword” to cut off the contaminated part of the Bubble Universe - The so-called “European continent” and its corresponding high-dimensional structure.</speak>
            <goto goto="40" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="fractalBigBang.jpg">
            <bgm src="bigTask.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">The second step is to blast the cut off part into dust, so that it will be gone forever from this Bubble Universe.</speak>
            <goto goto="50" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="CG27-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="bigTask.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">I think you already came to understand that the structure of the Bubble is essentially a set of “manifolds” in a high-dimensional space.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">At first glance, it looks like a complete universe; But in reality it’s more like an “atlas” floating on the Sea of Quanta bound together in different places.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">By that metaphor, the Wall of Honkai and the European continent behind it are molds growing on this atlas.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Valkyries, this may be your first time here - But the Republic has been fighting these parasites for over half a century.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">If we are rooted on this land to endure this protracted war, the same goes for the other side.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">The enemy has already turned their side on a paradise for Honkai; And one day they might turn the entire world into a monster-ridden demon realm.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Therefore, if there’s any chance left of victory, then it must be to remove the entire enemy power, alongside the soil which they depend on, from this world.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">...Fortunately we live in a Bubble Universe, not a perfect world.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">On this folded atlas, we have the chance to tear away the “Devil’s illustrations” from this book.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">...And the “paper cutter” that can accomplish that is the holy sword in your hand, which came here after crossing several worlds.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">--Yes, Bianka, no need to be surprised. The complete “Durandal” is a weapon capable of cutting space itself.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Many years ago it was theoretically proven and tried to be put in practice--</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">But sadly the experiment failed.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">At the time, there was no one strong enough to be the “Holy Swordsman”.</speak>
            <goto goto="60" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="palaceMeetingQuito.jpg">
            <bgm src="legion.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <show chara="thorSighClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">We have to admit… Not even Rowland was capable of it. Not even Star Whisperers can handle the maximum output of the Holy Sword, let alone a normal human.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">However, you Valkyries are true warriors who fight the honkai: Your possibilities are completely different from us, Captain Shakespeare or Dr. Schrodinger.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">...Bianka Ataegina, I believe you are our missing puzzle piece.</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Therefore, I will tell you the whereabouts of the last gems from “Durandal”--</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">In addition to the two in my hand and the one in possession of Shigure Kira, the seventh gem you are looking for--</speak>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Is in the far away Rapa Nui Island from the South Pacific.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Regardless of whether you agree to our plan or not: Once you return with the gem in hand, I will hand over the two in my possession to its original owner.</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">After all, it’s much more valuable to have them all gathered in the right hands than being used individually by different minded people.</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">And like I said before, if the plan succeeds, I will provide you with something much more valuable than these gems in return.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="back"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">So, will you think about it? Valkyries, Captain Shakespeare?</speak>
            <goto goto="70" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="submarineDoctorRoom.jpg">
            <bgm src="theme.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">How do you feel, Dudu? In an hour, you will be able to return to your perfect form.</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="durandalOpen" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">Hmm.. if you ask me, it honestly doesn’t feel real. </speak>
            <show chara="durandalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">Maybe it’s because all of my functions are separated on various crystals...</speak>
            <show chara="durandalWhite" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">But I can’t imagine what it feels like to “Cut space itself”.</speak>
            <show chara="durandalOpen" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">But since Dr. Schrodinger didn’t refute the Chairwoman’s statements, I think the complete me can probably do that kind of thing.</speak>
            <show chara="durandalStare" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">Having said that, my new master - You usually won’t take the initiative to talk to me, right?</speak>
            <show chara="durandalSquint" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">So what are you nervous about?</speak>
            <show chara="durandalSquint" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShoutClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Hey! Don’t talk nonsense!</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSneerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Why would I be nervous? I’m an A-Rank Valkyrie, what kind of storms have I not been through?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">……</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Well, that might be too much. Forget what I said.</speak>
            <hide position="left"></hide>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <bgm src="05_01_themeEin.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_SchrodingerNoName">“This much you should understand:”</speak>
            <speak chara="_SchrodingerNoName">“The immortal is omnipresent”</speak>
            <speak chara="_SchrodingerNoName">“Nothing can kill him”</speak>
            <speak chara="_SchrodingerNoName">“It is immovable, solid and eternal”</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">--Huh, Dr. Schrodinger?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">“It birthed all creation”</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">“I am the origin of all things”</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">“And I am the destroyer of all things”</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">“O, Arjuna”</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Uh… Are you reciting a poem?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger" remark="next">They are chapters from the “Bhagavad Gita”. A long time ago, an alumni who really likes Hindu culture read it for me.</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX18q0ylbT3AnO+SGT5Pt">
                <p class="article-text-h">注：</p>
                <p class="article-text">《薄伽梵歌》（भगवद् गीता，意为“至尊神的赞歌”），是印度教的重要经典，叙述了阿周那与黑天（奎师那）在俱卢之野战争打响前的一段长谈——因此，史诗《摩诃婆罗多》对它也进行了全文引用。（学术界认为《薄伽梵歌》全篇于公元前五世纪到公元后三世纪之间陆续写成，其起源早于《摩诃婆罗多》的成书时间。）</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. 《薄伽梵歌》是唯一一本记录【神本人】而不是【神的代言人】或者【先知】言论的印度教经典，因此在印度教与印度文化中都具有独一无二的特殊地位（可以类比东亚文化圈的《论语》）。</p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...I think your current self might be similar to the “Arjuna before the war” in the poem.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Who’s Arjuna?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">A prince and a great hero in the Hindu mythology.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Before the battle of Kurukshretra he saw many of his friends and relatives on the enemy side, so he was disappointed and wanted to stop fighting.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">And the “Bhagavad Gita” is the speech that the god Krishna gave him to persuade him to take part in the war.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...But I don’t have any friends or relatives on the opposite side of the battlefield?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Indeed. It would be impossible for you to meet an acquaintance here.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Bianka, you problem is the exact of opposite of Arjuna’s--</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">--And because of that, the way you feel might be similar.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressHesitateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...I don’t get what you mean.</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressHesitateClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I mean - You and the enemy you will soon face have neither companionship or conflict with each other.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">And yet - No, because of that, there is still hesitation, confusion and even fear in your heart.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressHesitateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">……</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressHesitateClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">You Valkyries are just passersby in this world; The reason you crossed the Sea of Quanta wasn’t to “Help the world”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Quite the contrary - If my understanding of Schicksal is correct, then they would actually want you to “bring home” something from this world.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressAngryClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">……</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressAngryClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">It’s fine - You can take Durandal back, as long as it is fine with that.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Moreover, if the Chairwoman’s plan works, it shouldn't pose a problem to ask for a copy of the info on the “Ether Anchor”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">So you should relax - Although personally “Otto Apocalypse” is a deadly enemy, I won’t be interfering with your mission.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Wait… “Deadly enemy”? That sloppy Otto?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Yes. “Can’t share the sky”, “Water and fire”, “Positive and negative”, “Target to be killed”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">However, telling you about our history won’t do you any good, and it has nothing to do with the point I was trying to make.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Bianka, until now you have just been following the Captain’s or the Chairwoman’s plan - You haven’t thought about your place in this matter.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">You have nothing to feel responsible about - And that’s the source of your tension.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">You feel like an outsider. You are afraid of failing to meet the expectations of the people from this world.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressHateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">……</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressHateClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I asked Rita about you. She said you are a very motivated Valkyrie--</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">--But what brings you joy is not the process, but the result of the missions.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...And I think that’s a painful and unnecessary way to think.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressHesitateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">But--</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressHesitateClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Bianka, if you only look at the results, there are plenty of things in this world that are meaningless… Or at least their meaning is unclear.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">What is the meaning of being born? The meaning of death? What about the “self”? Does mankind, the world and the universe have any meaning?</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Are you telling me that these things don’t have any meaning?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSighClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">No, they do. But learning it can't be achieved by consequentialism, that’s all.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">……</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">For example, Bianka, the meaning of your existence is “Yourself”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">For your senior Valkyries, you are a “motivation” by forcing them to chase after you;</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">For your overseer, you are a rare specimen;</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">For the people in this Bubble Universe, you are a heroic superwoman;</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">And for yourself, it’s the life that you started from scratch under the name “Bianka”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">None of them are a “result”, they started from “nothing” and will end with “nothing”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger"> Bianka, the “salvation” that this Bubble seeks is not a result, but a process, a movement.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...A movement?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Yes. A spiritual totem named “Superhero”, a temple living in everyone’s hearts.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">--Like the movement of Wagner or Richard Strauss.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...From another perspective, it’s quite similar to Shigure Kira’s idol work.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Valkyrie, you have the ability to complete your “world-class performance” on the “Stage of the World”--</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">--And it doesn’t matter that not even one atom of yours is from this world.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Do you understand? According to Bhagavan, each one of us is an “actor” chosen by the “director” named “Destiny”--</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">--Just release your energy on the stage to your heart’s content! Use the method you are most familiar with!</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressScreamClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Is it that simple?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressScreamClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">It’s that simple. That is the so-called “Fate’s screenplay”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">There was never a “Valkyrie of Schicksal” in here; Only artists in the “Spiritual Temple” and “idols” on the “Stage of the World”.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Remember: As long you are yourself, you are perfect.</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Besides, “being yourself” is the kind of behavior that best meets “the director’s expectations”, if I explain it like that you understand it better?</speak>
            <show chara="schroNoSwordSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">……！</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileAhClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Yes! If you explain it like that, I understand it very clearly!</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSneerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">In my case, I’m the kind who charges forward courageously at everything!</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileAhClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Thank you, Dr. Schrodinger! I feel like I understand everything now!</speak>
            <goto goto="80" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="chileRiverMountain.jpg">
            <bgm src="peerGynt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>One hour later--</text>
            <show chara="biankaDressSneerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Chairwoman! This red samurai has been brought back without losing a single strand of hair - I will return her to you now.</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSneerClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Fufu. Thank you, Valkyrie. Sure enough, you have found a method that combines the best of both worlds.</speak>
            <hide position="left"></hide>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">...Sanada. Thank you for all your hard work.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="yukimuraColdClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Yukimura">I’m afraid that “hard work” is the fate of both the samurais and of the Sanada clan.</speak>
            <show chara="yukimuraSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Yukimura">Having said that… It would be great if I had some hot soba to eat now.</speak>
            <show chara="yukimuraSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Hot soba would be a bit too hard... Do you mind if it’s Baumkuchen instead?</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="yukimuraTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Yukimura">Baumkuchen? Isn’t that exquisite?</speak>
            <show chara="yukimuraTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">It’s a special occasion for you. What, does it not suit your tastes?</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="yukimuraSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Yukimura">Haha, don’t worry. A samurai should treat their appetite with care, even before their death - That’s what my teacher taught me long ago.</speak>
            <show chara="yukimuraTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Yukimura">Ah, you don’t know about my past...</speak>
            <show chara="yukimuraTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Do you mean Ishida Mitsunari?</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="yukimuraTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Yukimura">Huh?</speak>
            <show chara="yukimuraTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="thorSighClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Alas, you should be more confident in your reputation, “Crimson Demon of War”.</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Back on topic, Bianka--</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">….Yes?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">Here are the gems I promised. Take them.</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">As for the idol who witnessed your actions--</speak>
            <show chara="ShigureKiraSunGlassesOffConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_ShigureKira">--Of course, no problem.</speak>
            <show chara="ShigureKiraSunGlassesOffTalkingClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_ShigureKira">Bianka, this is the “Idol Stone” that represents love and perfection.</speak>
            <show chara="ShigureKiraSunGlassesOffConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_ShigureKira">I am now officially lending it to you.</speak>
            <show chara="ShigureKiraSunGlassesOffConfidentClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileAhClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">….Thanks.</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileAhClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="durandalOutstretchOpen" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_SwordDurandalQ">So without further ado, should I take them all unceremoniously?</speak>
            <show chara="durandalOutstretchOpen" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Yes. The seven gems, at this moment, will be returned to their original owner.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesCasualLaughClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">The Holy Sword! Let everyone see your true appearance once more!</speak>
            <goto goto="90" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="CG1.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The red Gem of Courage symbolizes the determination to be brave and adventurous;</text>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="CG2-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The orange Gem of Intuition symbolizes the dream of self-confidence and exploration;</text>
            <goto goto="110" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="110" background="CG4-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The golden Gem of Freedom symbolizes the perfection and love of yourself;</text>
            <goto goto="120" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="120" background="CG7-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The green Gem of Ethics symbolizes the power of kindness and justice;</text>
            <goto goto="130" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="130" background="CG16-1-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The cyan Gem of Prosperity symbolizes the vitality and tenacity of life;</text>
            <goto goto="140" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="140" background="CG21-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The blue Gem of Reason symbolizes the wisdom of reason and insight;</text>
            <goto goto="150" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="150" background="CG25-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_22_Tiger.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The purple Gem of Dominance symbolizes nobility and the unification of all things.</text>
            <goto goto="160" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="160" background="CG27-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>“Calm down, foundation of the universe”</text>
            <text>“I am timespace itself.”</text>
            <text>“The source of the power that destroys all.”</text>
            <text>“My role is to obliterate all universes”</text>
            <goto goto="170" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="170" background="CG27-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">You… turned out to be such a powerful weapon, Durandal!</speak>
            <speak chara="_HolySwordDurandal">It’s because I have a strong master, Miss Bianka Ataegina.</speak>
            <speak chara="_HolySwordDurandal">In your hands, I undoubtedly have the power to destroy any land on this Bubble Universe.</speak>
            <speak chara="_HolySwordDurandal">But I hope you understand: Every weapon’s function is destruction and violence. Even the so-called “Holy Sword” is no exception.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...I know that.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">The Valkyrie education made me understand that long ago: Violence has its original sin, but beyond that, it has no good or evil in itself.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...The real good and evil lies in the motives and consequences of using violence.</speak>
            <goto goto="180" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="180" background="chileRiverMountain.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_21_dannyBoy_p.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="champoBlanketSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Champollion">Confucius said, “"Only the virtuous can be benevolent to the wicked.</speak>
            <show chara="champoBlanketSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Champollion">There is no evil in pursuing benevolence."</speak>
            <show chara="champoBlanketNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Champollion">Voltaire admired Confucius because he saw the shadow of his ideal “Human Legislator” in him.</speak>
            <show chara="champoBlanketSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Champollion">He believed that Confucius’s “benevolence” symbolized the moral harmony between individual and society, and represented the true kindness and freedom of mankind.</speak>
            <show chara="champoBlanketSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Champollion">Bianka… You now represent that power of “benevolence and righteousness”; Voltaire would certainly praise you as being the most perfect “Valkyrie”.</speak>
            <show chara="champoBlanketSmileClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Dr. Champollion… Don’t praise me so suddenly. You’re embarrassing me.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">I… I haven’t even done anything yet.</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="champoBlanketLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Champollion">Hahaha, forgive me. My mood is a bit agitated, and I accidentally took on the bragging atmosphere of a certain era.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">“One man has faith that he may eat all things.”</speak>
            <show chara="thorSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">The Sun is just one more star; And similarly, you don’t need to care too much about the praise of others.</speak>
            <hide position="left"></hide>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">At this moment, only one thing matters:</speak>
            <show chara="thorAngryClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau">For the first time in fifty years - no, in history, we have the power to strategically eliminate the enemy.</speak>
            <show chara="thorNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau"> --We should strike while the iron is hot. I will now announce the specific tactical plan of “Operation Pachakutiq”.</speak>
            <show chara="thorConfidentClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_Thoreau" remark="next">In the name of the “Reformer of the world”, let’s perform an earth-shaking operation!</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19MJFfogqWmorFMiux7">
                <p class="article-text-h">注：</p>
                <p class="article-text">帕查库特克（Pachakutiq，直译“翻转天地的人”，通译“大地震撼者”）是印加帝国最伟大的一位“萨帕·印卡”（相当于“皇帝”）：“他登基前，印加人还只是生活在简朴的村社群落里；到他去世时，印加人已管理着一个扩张主义的大帝国了”。</p>
            </remark>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX1+rrYOcUkuxFXqZbI1s"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
