<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_12_mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="11_12_newChapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="parisPalace.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>Everyone abandons their past in the process of their lives.</text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">As we grow older, we gradually leave our mother’s womb and breasts, the warm and comfortable cradle, leave the place where we were raised, and eventually we become a person with no semblance of our past selves.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Shimotsuki 27th.</p>
                <p class="article-text">13 of the Portuguese month.</p>
                <p class="article-text">13th of the month.</p>
                <p class="article-text">18th and 19th of Brumaire.</p>
                <p class="article-text">Fengyue 8th.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">It was this series of betrayals that made the man named “Napoleon Bonaparte” finally become the version written in history.</p>
            </text>
            <text>He had long gotten accustomed to being betrayed, and was even proud of it.</text>
            <text>No matter what the situation is… as long as there was a chance for a comeback, he would definitely continue to move forward.</text>
            <text>--The word “failure” was never in his dictionary.</text>
            <text>In previous wars, limited by equipment, supplies, morale and luck, he also had to helplessly surrender, and was afraid that a comeback would not be possible.</text>
            <text>However, all of that, to this day, is nothing more than history he has long trampled on.</text>
            <text>He was defeated by the Russian “General Winter”, and the enemy’s coalition commander drove straight and directly occupied Paris.</text>
            <text>But in the blink of an eye, he sneaked out of Elba Island and went back to his homeland, with all of Bourbon's army turning to his side.</text>
            <text>However, the subsequent battle of Waterloo brought the Hundred Days to a hasty end. He was punished with exile for the second time, now to the distant South Atlantic Ocean--</text>
            <text>But just when everyone thought that the Emperor’s life would not bring any new upheavals, he who was in his twilight years, was involved in the experiments of the “Snake” and sent to another world by mistake. He regained his throne.</text>
            <text>However, his life that should have been smooth sailing was corrupted by greed: In order to permanently master this mighty power, he tried to activate the ancient civilization’s device to control this microverse.</text>
            <text>...Therefore turning all of his subjects into inhuman existences. </text>
            <goto goto="20" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="parisPalaceDark.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>But even so, the emperor did not give up.</text>
            <text>After a brief period of grief, he realized that this was just the beginning of a greater journey--</text>
            <text>He and his surviving subjects had just transformed from a lifeform that “consumes chemical energy” into another lifeform that “consumes Honkai Energy”.</text>
            <text>The position of emperor remains solid. The empire's military power was better than ever.</text>
            <text>After a brief dispute, the subjects of today became single-hearted, with a sincerity more enthusiastic and majestic than the previous “Era of Hymns”</text>
            <text>Although the new subjects needed a “Wall” to gradually transform the land under their feet - To the emperor, this slow but sure expansion brought a different kind of calmness.</text>
            <goto goto="30" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="spaceNight.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>Which is why, currently the emperor can be said to be extremely angry.</text>
            <text>He originally thought that, as the world gradually turned into one more suitable for his people’s lives, his enemies would only become weaker and less aggressive--</text>
            <text>However, those ants that only stay in their nest, the Girondin-like mobs, the stupid humans incapable of accepting the new form of life…</text>
            <text>They were able to disintegrate part of the world. They were able to destroy the sacred and energy filled territory of his empire.</text>
            <text>They were able to push the emperor into despair without losing a single soldier.</text>
            <goto goto="40" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="CG28-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>...But that did not waver the emperor.</text>
            <text>He had lived for so long, that this was just a new form of “despair”.</text>
            <text>The enemy seemed to believe that the foundation of the empire’s existence was its sacred territory. </text>
            <text>“Without a land, a country cannot exist” - Usually, that would be true.</text>
            <text>However, thanks to the barrier of the “wall”, they could not infer that…</text>
            <text>...The emperor and his subjects had already become inseparable, and even if they were scattered in the void, there is still a way to preserve the core functions.</text>
            <goto goto="50" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="01_19_scienceEngineWarning.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="center" opacity="0.6"/>
            <text>The empire was built upon the principle of the “new life”.</text>
            <text>It would eventually break out of its cocoon and become a butterfly, breaking through the cage called “the world”.</text>
            <text>There will be no disease, no discrimination, no poverty, and no death.</text>
            <text>--And after that, an absolute understanding and absolute freedom.</text>
            <text>They will reach the resurrection promised by the prophet to the people, and they will bring judgement to all lower lifeforms.</text>
            <text>As of now, it is a creature that is both the emperor and his subjects. The only thing it did not understand is…</text>
            <text>...Why this blazing power, until today, had not been inherited and carried forward by anyone?</text>
            <text>After all, the source of this power was not “Napoleon Bonaparte” or any wise man from his era-</text>
            <text>This power originated from a secret from tens of thousands of years in the past. It is like a rising sun in the eclipse, unfortunately dying before it could give off light.</text>
            <text>However, it had to wait for nightfall before it could shine majestically on the other side of the shore.</text>
            <goto goto="60" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="lavaEarth.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="wristClose-up" position="left"/>
            <text>...It discarded all forms of impurity, leaving only the strongest, simplest, and most original part of life.</text>
            <text>No language, no beauty. Just its existence was a symbol of truth.</text>
            <text>--This is undoubtedly the ultimate lifeform.</text>
            <text>Those who try to kill it in the cradle will only be humiliated in the face of this force.</text>
            <text>What’s more, the opponent’s formation was too dependent on the “tunnels” of this world--</text>
            <text>--In the eyes of the emperor, the opponent had lost from the start.</text>
            <goto goto="70" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="lavaFlow.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_04_Miracle.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>...The smell of blood was permeating the battlefield.</text>
            <text>The soldier’s bodies filled every nearby gully like sandbags being piled to prevent a flood.</text>
            <text>However, the temporary commander-in-chief was unable to order a retreat.</text>
            <text>The enemy landed from the sky, occupying the main entrance to the Anchor Point and cutting off everyone’s retreat.</text>
            <text>Therefore, as long as these commanders did not plan on leaving their soldiers to escape first-</text>
            <text>--They must choose for everyone, including themselves, to either “charge at the enemy” or “wait to die”.</text>
            <text>The enemy is firmly on their throats. The passage of the Anchor Point is easy to defend but difficult to attack.</text>
            <text>Bringing troops from the other side of the Bubble Universe will only cause them to be wiped out by this weird enemy before they can even get into formation.</text>
            <text>...At this moment, on this North Sea island, they can only fight alone.</text>
            <goto goto="80" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="CG28-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_04_Miracle.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>At first, when the gate-shaped monster appeared on the starry sky, the soldiers were optimistic that it was just some kind of residue from the cutting of the world--</text>
            <text>--It might be a leftover mechanical device, or an enemy that is only strong in groups.</text>
            <text>However, when neither the interception nor the bombardment worked, the enemy landed at the entrance of the Anchor Point like a city atop of a mountain and extended countless tentacles…</text>
            <text>...Everyone understood that what was standing before them was by no means an ordinary existence.</text>
            <goto goto="90" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="CG29-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_04_Miracle.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <sound src="01_19_claw.mp3"/>
            <cg src="01_19_bloodWhite.jpg" bg="CG29-1.jpg" fadeIn="0" fadeOut="1"></cg>
            <bgm src="01_04_Miracle.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>The soldiers of the Republic fought bravely.</text>
            <text>They fought as hard as they could, just to buy time for their companions.</text>
            <text>Newlyweds, new parents, only children, young people…</text>
            <text>The corps stranded on the island followed that order, using the channels still under their control to evacuate their comrades one by one.</text>
            <text>If you compare the information flux, the “bandwidth” of this alternate Anchor Channel is only about 1/10000th of the main channel--</text>
            <text>That means that for every hour that the soldiers persist on the frontline, only 20 people can successfully retreat.</text>
            <text>--And today, in order to perfectly implement the plan of cutting the Bubble Universe, on this small North Sea island, nearly 3000 of the most elite warriors of the Republic have gathered.</text>
            <text>...That is to say, even if the frontline soldiers can continue to support them, it would still take them a week to be completely evacuated from the island.</text>
            <text>Of course, they also have the “Caledonia” that can traverse this world’s unique underwater gusts and waves--</text>
            <text>But even this extra means, at full capacity, can only transfer 50 lucky people every two days.</text>
            <goto goto="100" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="CG29-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="07_07_wind.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">--Bianka and the holy sword have consumed too much energy in the previous operation. Even with Rita’s care, she seems unable to wake up in a short time.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">The Star Whisperers under your command, and even the crew of the “Caledonia”, who think they can survive on the battlefield, have already rushed to the front line.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">Every one of them is brave… But they should know it best-</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">--They are fighting a losing battle.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThoreauNoName">...So what?</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThoreauNoName">If you have an idea that can change the situation around, don’t be afraid.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThoreauNoName">Tell it to me now.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">I think… if the things I consulted with Dr. Schrodinger ten days ago are indeed true, then I have a way to kill that gate--</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">--But I need you to order everyone to leave the battlefield.</speak>
            <goto goto="110" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="110" background="CG29-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="noise.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">...What did you say? Retreat? Leave the battle?</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">Are you crazy? We are now fighting each other, where do you want me to retreat to?</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">--Do you want me to abandon the only defensive position and retreat directly to headquarters?</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">This is military suicide, you know?</speak>
            <goto goto="120" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="120" background="CG29-4.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ChampollionNotSure">...Don’t panic, Wallachian.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ChampollionNotSure">The Chairwoman ordered you to retreat for a reason--</speak>
            <speak chara="_ChampollionNotSure">--Because now, I will be responsible for destroying this enemy.</speak>
            <goto goto="130" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="130" background="CG29-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">...You? An archeologist?</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">Did you convince her by changing your clothes a little?</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">...What on earth are you going to do?</speak>
            <goto goto="140" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="140" background="CG29-4.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ChampollionNotSure">First of all, I want to apologize to you--</speak>
            <speak chara="_ChampollionNotSure">Because the name “Champollion” I have been using in front of you is actually just borrowed from a compatriot of a younger generation.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ChampollionNotSure">Let me introduce myself again, strong warriors and brave soldiers--</speak>
            <speak chara="_ThinkerChampollion">My name is “Napoleon”, and my surname is “Bonaparte” - I am from Corsica.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">I am not an ordinary “Star Whisperer”. I am the “life of the ordinary people” that was discarded by the monster in front of you when he was twenty five years old--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">--I am the first and the source of the countless “betrayals” that it has long forgotten.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">After borrowing the spare channel and adjusting myself with the Anchor Point, I have returned to the original state from when I was abandoned by this monster, and have deliberately reversed the Imaginary Polarity of my body structure.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">To put it simply, at this moment, the monster in front of you can’t hurt me at all--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">--But I can completely destroy it with a single touch.</speak>
            <goto goto="150" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="150" background="CG29-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">That’s...</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">If there was such a convenient way, why are you only doing this now?!</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">...Do you know just how many people we have sacrificed?!</speak>
            <goto goto="160" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="160" background="CG29-5.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">...I’m sorry.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">I let everyone suffer such great sacrifices here… I am really sorry.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">But no matter what the purpose is… If one wants to take initiative to give up on their life...</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">--They will still struggle to prepare their heart for that.</speak>
            <goto goto="170" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="170" background="CG29-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">You...</speak>
            <speak chara="_Dracula">Are you going to die together with it?!</speak>
            <goto goto="180" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="180" background="CG29-6.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_Hero.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">...To be precise, I’m just letting it “bury” me.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">Readjusting the Imaginary Polarity of the physical structure of the entire body - That is a suicidal act by itself.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">I am nothing more than a walking corpse--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">--I just want to find a place where I can be buried in glory.</speak>
            <goto goto="190" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="190" background="CG29-7.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_19_bellaCiao.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">...It’s the same for me and for “Napoleon Bonaparte”.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">Do you now feel humiliated because of my presence?</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">Does my presence scare you?</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">You who have been denying yourself in your long life, but in turn was denied by your own past--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">You who have been integrated with all your subjects and lost your speaking organs, do you feel indignant at this moment?</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">Or are you too busy trying to move your bulky body, trying to avoid the death that approaches you step by step?</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">...Ah. All of that, to me, is not important.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">I just want you to know--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">You have gone so terribly astray--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">That your history, your original intentions, your original dream--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">--Would rather use its own death in exchange for your destruction.</speak>
            <goto goto="200" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="200" background="CG29-8.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_19_bellaCiao.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">...Bianka.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">When you hold the Holy Sword again, you might feel sad because of what happened at this moment.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure"> We are travelling companions, adventurers constantly exploring in order to save the world;</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">But today, the world also endured a lot of unnecessary pain due to my hesitation.</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">But, having said that--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">If it’s you--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">You will certainly raise your head higher, keep walking at your usual pace, and move on unwavering, right?</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">Because you already know, only this way can this imperfect story become perfect--</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">And the imperfect world will have the tomorrow that everyone looks forward to.</speak>
            <goto goto="210" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="210" background="white.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_19_bellaCiao.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">Bianka… And Rita, who is always by your side…</speak>
            <speak chara="_NapoleonNotSure">...You also think so, right?</speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX1+oXCYaOQzPLggAhFhF"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
